Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The entire world is white.
What am I doing here?
That's right. I've been here with her all this time.
I've been here with only her...
...in this sad world where there is nothing.
If this was going to happen,
I shouldn't have brought her out.
I only brought her suffering.
That's right.
I probably shouldn't have spoken to Nagisa at this moment.
If she hadn't met me, Nagisa wouldn't have...
Is this the end of our journey?
I didn't want it to be.
I didn't want her to go to sleep in such a cold place.
Hey.
You're there, right?
Of course. I'm always by your side.
Thank you.
Eh?
I can finally hear your voice.
You're right!
I soon won't be a human,
so I can hear your voice, too.
I was having a dream.
I learned a lot of things in it.
About myself. About you.
Will you listen to them?
Yeah.
You and I used to be in the same world.
We were very close, too. Long ago, though.
Actually, we might still be.
So we weren't supposed to be in this world, after all!
Let's go back together.
I'm sorry. I have to remain here.
Why?
Because, in this world, I am the world.
I don't understand! We promised!
We promised we'd leave this world together.
If I leave this world, this world will disappear.
Then many lights would meet misery.
Lights?
You mean all those lights that were flying?
Yes. Those are feelings from people in the other world.
You were one of the lights, too.
The world that is furthest,
yet the world that is closest.
We've always been there.
Yes, we came from the same place.
We only see things differently.
Another world? Is an alternate me there?
You should be able to tell,
since you exist in both worlds.
We were able to meet despite the differences in the world.
That's enough to make me content.
You will soon fall asleep in this world and wake up in the other world.
You'll meet many people,
and many things will happen.
Then you'll eventually meet me.
I'll be able to see you again?
In the other world?
Like we can see people's feelings from the other world as light in this world,
my feelings will become many lights in that world and shimmer.
Each light may be very faint, but gathered together they should become a strong force.
I know that song.
Yes. It's the song you always sang for me.
Good bye, Daddy.
Nagisa!!!
Nagisa!
I'm right here!
Tomoya-kun.
I'm glad you stopped me.
Nagisa...
I was really worried you might be thinking that you should have never met me.
I'm glad that I met you.
I had a wonderful life.
Nagisa.
So please. Don't lose yourself.
No matter what may await,
please don't regret meeting me.
Is that too much to ask?
You're right...
Thank you.
Would you like me to take you?
To a place in this city where wishes come true.
It's coming to an end...
...The long, long journey...
Nagisa?
Nagisa...
Tomoya-kun.
Nagisa!
Is something wrong, Tomoya-kun?
We were just together, weren't we?
We're always together.
We said that we'd always be.
Yeah, you're right.
Okazaki-san.
Both the baby and your wife are safe now.
You've done a great job.
You did great, too.
Thanks.
Tomoya-san.
Will you give Ushio her first bath?
Ah, yes!
Support the head with your right hand.
Plug the ears so the water doesn't get in.
Yes, slowly.
There, doesn't it feel good?
Don't dip the head in yet.
Wipe it with the gauze.
Ushio-chan, isn't it great to be washed by your Daddy?
Great job, Tomoya-kun.
She's a very active baby.
I hope she'll continue to be active even after she grows.
Don't worry!
She'll be a strong girl, in both body and mind.
We'll make sure of that!
Yes.
Tomoya-kun. Take a look outside the window.
It's very beautiful.
You mean the snow?
No, this is...
Dango, dango, dango, dango.
Dango, a great big dango family.
A great big dango family.
If a city has a heart and a mind like people do,
and if it's trying to make the people living in it as happy as possible,
INSERT SONG PLACEHOLDER
then a miracle like this could be
something the city accomplished.
INSERT SONG PLACEHOLDER
Tooku de tooku de yureteru inaho no umi
Far, far away is a sea of rice swaying.
遠くで遠くで揺れてる稲穂の海
But that's not exactly a miracle, is it?
INSERT SONG PLACEHOLDER
The people that love the city live there,
and the city that loves people will love the people.
It's something that should be happening anywhere.
INSERT SONG PLACEHOLDER
Ho wo age ho wo age mezashita omoide heto
帆を上げ帆を上げ目指した思い出へと
Cast, cast off, and sail to where the memories are.
We love the city, and we're being nurtured by the city.
INSERT SONG PLACEHOLDER
The city is a big family, eh?
Yes. Just like the Big Dango Family.
Yeah.
I think I finally understand, too.
We will hold or lose memories of the things that happened to this day.
Bokura ha kyou made no kanashii koto zenbu oboeteruka wasuretaka
僕らは今日までの悲しいこと全部覚えてるか、忘れたか
In the small hand is the strength to pass us one day.
小さな手にもいつからか僕ら追い越してく強さ
Chiisana te nimo itsukaraka bokura oikoshiteku tsuyosa
Many days have passed since the day
you sat and cried under the ripe grapes.
熟れた葡萄の下泣いてた日から歩いた
Ureta budou no shita naiteta hi kara aruita
小さな手でも離れても僕らはこの道ゆくんだ
Chiisana te demo hanarete mo bokura ha kono michi yukunda
Even when the small hand leaves us,
we will continue on our way.
いつかくる日は一番の思い出を仕舞って
Itsuka kuru hi ha ichiban no omoide wo shimatte
We'll face the special day sure to come with our best memory.
Seasons have gone by and a cold wind blows.
季節は移り　もう冷たい風が
Kisetsu ha utsuri mou tsumetai kaze ga
Sleep within that song sung by the spring.
Tsutsumarete nemure ano haru no uta no naka de
包まれて眠れ　あの春の歌の中で
Chiisana te nimo itsukaraka bokura oikoshiteku tsuyosa
In the small hand is the strength to pass us one day.
小さな手にもいつからか僕ら追い越してく強さ
Nureta hoho niha doredake no egao ga utsutta
Many wet cheeks were sacrificed for smiles.
濡れた頬にはどれだけの笑顔が映った
Chiisana te demo hanarete mo bokura ha kono michi yukunda
Even when the small hand leaves us,
we will continue on our way.
小さな手でも離れても僕らはこの道ゆくんだ
When the special day comes, we will save it as a memory.
そして来る日は僕らも思い出を仕舞った
Soshite kuru hi ha bokura mo omoide wo shimatta
The small hand will eventually pass us.
小さな手でもいつの日か僕ら追い越してゆくんだ
Chiisana te demo itsuno hika bokura oikoshite yukunda
Yagate kuru hi ha atarashii kisetsu wo hiraita
The special day is the start of a new season.
やがて来る日は新しい季節を開いた
Don't be so upset.
Fuko is very upset.
That person was very rude.
Fuko isn't a grade school kid.
You're very small, so you can't blame them for the mistake.
Even if Fuko's small, Fuko wants them to sense the adult aura Fuko gives off.
You're not giving that off as much as you think.
That really stabbed into Fuko's heart.
Fuko's really hurt.
Fuko's been tainted!
Don't say strange things.
Fuko's an adult!
Oh, maybe it's that.
How you speak in the third person may be the reason people see you as a child.
How should Fuko speak then?
"Me"?
You know, me's already mature enough.
Like that?
That was so illicit sounding!
Don't jab at your own action.
Just say "I" like everyone else does.
"I"?
You know, I'm already mature enough.
Like that?
That was so illicit sounding!
I think it would sound illicit no matter how you say it so long as it's that line.
Fuko's hungry.
So you've given up already, eh?
Fuko wants to go to a family restaurant.
Let's go after the check up.
There's nothing wrong with Fuko anymore.
So we're going now!
No!
If we don't hurry,
the hamburgers will be sold out.
There are plenty, so don't worry.
They would be gone if everyone had been ordering only hamburgers starting a week ago.
Such a coincidence can't happen, so don't worry.
There, we're almost at the hospital.
If the hamburgers are sold out,
I'll make one for you.
Will it be served on an iron plate
so it won't get cold?
It will, it will.
Then okay.
Besides, even if you're physically all right,
we need to periodically check your health.
I'll be at ease if they tell me that you're doing well.
Okay?
Fuko's making you worry?
No, not that much.
Please dissect Fuko all you want
so you'll be at ease!
Fu-chan!
Onee-chan! You're a slow walker!
Let's move along!
Why is she like this?
What is it this time, Fu-chan?
Fuko can smell.
The smell of a hamburger?
Don't treat me the same as you!
I was trying to talk at the same level as you.
That was very rude of you.
Fuko will repeat, so please ask what Fuko smells.
Okay, okay.
Fuko can smell.
What do you smell?
This smell is...
It's a cute smell.
That's not really an answer.
Fuko was hoping you would catch the nuance.
Was it a riddle?
You're being rude. It's an art.
You're talking more nonsense again.
Do you realize what you're saying, Fu-chan?
You were a teacher,
so you're too much of a realist.
I was an art teacher.
Art.
You see?
Then please capture what Fuko says.
There's nothing to capture.
Okay...
Then Fuko will say it simply.
I'll repeat again, so ask Fuko what the smell is.
Okay.
Someone's there.
What?
That's not what you're supposed to say.
The statement changed.
I'm supposed to ask,
"What do you smell?" to that statement?
Yes.
That would make me a strange person.
Don't worry. Fuko will follow you up.
One more time.
Okay.
Someone's there.
What do you smell?
I'm sure she's here to meet me.
You didn't follow me up at all.
Why aren't you surprised?
Fuko said someone's here to meet Fuko.
I hope she'll make lots of friends.
One more time.
As you wish.
Someone's there.
What do you smell?
I'm sure she's here to meet me.
What do you mean?
It's a cute smell.
You're not making any sense.
She's sleeping there.
She's waiting to be woken up by someone.
So...
Fuko's off!
Fu-chan! Where are you going?
You should come fast if you want to meet her, too.
She's under that tree!
Is someone there?
Fuko doesn't know!
But she's a very cute girl!
Fu-chan!
Hey, Fu-chan!
Really, she's such a...
Are you there? It's Fuko.
What's your name?
Would you tell Fuko?
Let's be friends and play together.
The fun is only just about to begin.
Even as a junior, it took me a lot of time to become friends with my classmates.
So you're alone in the class like always.
I couldn't talk with anyone, so I was a little lonely.
It'll be nice if you can make friends in your class soon.
Yes.
It was my first time talking to him,
so I was a little nervous.
Okazaki Tomoya.
What's yours?