Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We began to build a vehicle that can fly.
We'll leave this place with this...
...and we'll go to a more fun and livelier world.
If it gets cold, she won't be able to move.
We have to hurry.
We worked without rest.
Are you done with
your parent-teacher conference?
Yes. And since I can't think of something I want to study at college, I'm thinking of finding a job.
And you've got good grades, too... What a waste.
What will you do once you graduate?
Hey... Is there anything you want as a present?
Is it related to graduation?
No, not really, but I suddenly felt the urge to give you something.
You're trying to change the subject again.
I can't accept a present for no reason.
Isn't wanting to give something to
your loved one a good enough reason?
If that was true, then I'd have to give you something every day.
Anyway, if we stick to these rules,
then gift exchanges would happen only on birthdays and at Christmas.
In this case, I'd have only one day to receive presents.
Why?
I was born on December 24th.
Why did you have to be born on that day of all days?
Please complain about that to Dad and Mom.
All right! Let's go on a date.
A date?
If you're not going to take a present, then a date it is.
Happy?
Yes.
I'm happy.
I'm going to head up now.
Yes. I'll see you later.
No. We were talking about your future.
Tomoya-kun...
My future, eh?
Good morning, Okazaki!
And a toilet seat cover.
You already did that one before.
You've got a really gloomy face so early in the morning.
Did you have a fight with Nagisa-chan?
Hey... Have you figured out what you want to do after here?
Of course.
To not worry my lovely sister, I've thought things through seriously and have come to a conclusion!
Seriously?
Yeah! I'm going to make money with my looks!
A model, I tell you. A model!
A model?
I think I'm fit for a model.
It's possible to shift into entertainment business through modeling, too, right?
Crap!
I might become famous.
I'll put lots of young ones under
my spell and form the Sunohara Legion.
You really are an optimist.
My future is blessed!
It works! Sunohara-kun,
you can become a model!
Really?! Yay!
You'll become a really popular model.
You will be able to go into the entertainment industry and form the Sunohara Legion, too.
All right.
Okazaki! I'll draft you into my legion one day, too!
I'll look forward to it.
Everyone other than me is a senior here, aren't they?
Do you all know what you'll be doing after you graduate?
I'm planning on going to nursing school.
It's what I've wished to do for some time.
I'm aiming to become a kindergarten teacher.
So I'm going to a school that gives me the necessary degree.
I think... I'll be studying abroad in America.
It'll be sad to say goodbye to everyone,
but I'll come back to Japan as often as possible.
We won't be able to listen to your breathtaking violin anymore, huh?
If you crave for it, I can play it-
Stop!
Keep your thoughts to yourself.
You've got to learn to read into things a little more.
I'm sorry. I'm working on it, but...
She's being very rude.
What will you be doing, Okazaki-kun?
I heard you haven't even decided whether to go to college or get a job,
even running away from teachers.
Come on, Nagisa. You've got to spank Tomoya's butt more.
Nagisa?
What's wrong, Nagisa?
I'm sorry... I feel a little...
Nagisa!
She's got a fever.
You don't have to be with Nagisa-chan?
A doctor's at home right now.
If I'm there, I'm sure I'd make things awkward.
Come in.
Sunohara. You've got a phone call from your sister.
Righty-o.
Anything you want to say to her?
Tell her to come visit again.
Oh, but don't tell her Nagisa's sick.
Okay.
What do you mean?
Furukawa-san's sick?
She's not very healthy to begin with.
She's repeating this year because she was short on her attendance last year for the same reason.
I see.
Make sure you do a good job taking care of her.
Nagisa.
Yes.
Don't bother. Stay down.
Okay, thank you.
I'll get going.
Yes. Have a good day.
Get a good rest, okay?
Yes.
Aren't you worrying too much?
Puhi! Puhi! Puhi! Puhi! Puhi! Puhi! Puhi!
It's happened before, too, hasn't it?
Last time Nagisa-chan got sick, you were so out of your mind.
I mean, at crucial times, you're...
Puhi-puhi-puhi. Puhi.
Puhi!
Puhi?
Did you come to see Kyou, again?
Tomoya!
Puhi.
Oh, you weren't trying to eat him?
Don't attack before finding out!
What should we do with her? Can you go home alone?
Puhi puhi.
Looks like she wants to be with you.
Impossible. I have PE this afternoon.
Can you babysit her?
Why me?
That's not right. Besides,
I'm her owner, too, so I'll-
Puhi!
Puhi puhi puhi!
She doesn't like you?
No...
I tried to put her in the bath some time ago,
but the water was too hot and it made her think I was planning on stewing her.
Puhi puhi puhi puhi!
Puhi!
Therefore, take care of her.
You're gonna make me sit through class with this on my lap?
Puhi puhi...
Botan, doll!
Pu!
It's one of Botan's seven tricks.
If you hold her like that,
people will think of you as a doll-maniac.
What are you doing?
You owe me bigtime for this.
I'll treat you to fruit milk tomorrow.
That's not enough.
I'm so sorry about this.
We were thinking of paying a visit to Furukawa-san.
Oh, unfortunately, they said they were taking her to the hospital today.
I see. Then give her our best.
Yeah.
See you guys.
I hope it took his mind off things a little.
Puhi?
Puhi...
Tomoya-kun isn't happy.
He can be very sensitive at times.
I hope Nagisa-chan gets well soon.
A month went by.
Nagisa didn't get better.
One day, when she was feeling well, she forced her way to school.
But her fever went back up after only walking part-way to school.
How were exams?
So-so.
Thanks to attending more classes than before.
This is your test break.
Please don't worry about me and go play.
Let me stay here.
It'll be boring to stay here.
No, I'll wait here. That's enough fun for me.
Wait? Until what?
The day we can hold hands and walk.
We're together at home and school, but we didn't have much chance to be alone, right?
So I wanted to go on a date with you and hold hands.
We're alone right now.
Yeah.
Will you hold my hand?
November came.
With entrance exams coming, Seniors studied frantically.
In an environment like that,
the only thing on my mind was Nagisa.
Here are the tapes of theater you asked for.
I chose some that are fun and
give you energy just from watching.
Sorry for the trouble.
We owe you a big favor.
Thank you.
Okazaki-san, did you lose some weight?
It's your imagination.
Allow me to invite you to our, the cats' world, in return!
Wow, thank you!
The autumn went by like this.
The tension in the air started
to build, and winter drew near.
We figured you should know.
Okazaki-san. Nagisa might end up repeating her senior year again.
She can't take her exams,
and she'll be short on attendance, too.
The teachers said that she should withdraw from school and focus on getting better.
We are not worried about her educational record.
But Nagisa's...
We want to leave it to Nagisa to decide.
So even if she can't graduate, please accept that.
Please, Okazaki-san.
No.
I want to graduate with her.
I don't want to leave her behind there.
Okazaki-san...
If Nagisa isn't going to graduate, then I don't want to either.
What a child you are.
If you do something like that,
Nagisa will be hurt even more.
You understand that, don't you?
He was right.
I was a child.
I felt like I'd become a little better, being able to help some friends,
but the girl I love may not be able to graduate.
I was such a child that it was enough to put me at a loss.
When December came,
everything became busier.
Entrance exams.
College applications. Job searches.
I was left out of the groups.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Nagisa-chan.
And, Merry Christmas!
You sure have energy for a rejected applicant.
He seriously sent an application to a modeling agency.
It was my right to!
I'll be looking for a job near
my home next year, so it's fine!
Nagisa.
Here's my present.
It's Dango!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Being here for someone like me...
Don't say things like, "someone like me", Nagisa.
You're part of our precious family.
He's right. And our precious friend.
If you become happy, then so will Sanae and I.
So seize your happiness, Nagisa.
Yes. I'll do my best.
That was the Christmas Eve.
Nagisa's birthday,
and also the day Nagisa's need to repeat became definite.
After the New Years,
fewer seniors came to school.
I was with Nagisa.
Small and fragile, but someone who continued to work hard.
I wanted to protect her forever.
Sign: Hikarizaka Private High School Graduation
Sunohara. Want to go around breaking some windows after this?
What's that?
I thought I might be able to repeat the year if I did that.
Rather than being forced to repeat, you'd probably get kicked out.
Oh, right.
Then that's pointless.
Oh, Okazaki and Sunohara.
Congratulations for graduating.
Thanks.
I'll be retiring after this year, too.
I'll be graduating with you guys, I guess.
Really?
I was hoping the Theater Club
would be solid with you around.
Don't worry about her.
She's much stronger and
more level-headed than you two.
You two are the ones who have to try hard.
I was lucky to meet students who needed a lot of my attention in the end.
If you hadn't set us straight, we probably would've been kicked out long ago.
I've been wondering for a while, but did you purposely have Sunohara and me meet?
What do you mean?
Sunohara and I are similar.
When either has a friend,
neither would quit school that easily.
Isn't that what you thought?
I don't remember.
After all, I'm pretty old.
You guys will be members of society starting tomorrow.
Be sure you attend
your last homeroom, all right?
Thank you for your guidance.
Sign: Hikarizaka Private High School Graduation
Thanks for a lot of stuff.
That's for us to say.
It's been decided that the sakura trees will remain.
This is all thanks to you.
Nagisa will be in your class next year.
Please look after her.
We know. Don't worry about it.
Best of luck to you, Okazaki-san.
Tomoya!
We're headed to a party after this,
but you've got somewhere to go, don't you?
Yeah.
Sweet bean bread!
...shouted out a complete lie without thinking!
You idiot! You shouldn't be outside!
I wanted to see you no matter what.
You in your uniform.
Tomoya-kun. Congratulations on graduating.
Nagisa...
I graduated...
Yes.
I won't ever be a student at that school again.
I hated school,
but if it was with you,
I wanted to spend all my time there forever.
My student life was rotten as hell,
but the last year I spent with you was fun.
I was happy!
I should have repeated, too, after all.
Tomoya-kun.
You can't stop like that.
If you can move on, then you should.
Please move on.
I'll do my best for another year.
Tomoya-kun.
Can we hold hands?
You idiot. Your fever's going to go up again.
Just for a little.
I want to walk holding hands with you.
I wanted to keep on walking without stopping...
...walking on and on...
...even the endless uphill climb...
...just the two of us...
What are your plans from here?
Nothing in particular.
Do you want to work for us for a while?
I look forward to working with you, Tomoya-san.
"Tomoya-san"?
Please let me call you by name.
Since we're like family now.
Sign: Apartments