Edited at https://subtitletools.com
You went and brought more junk?
You're so cold.
Sorry I can't do anything.
Are you going?
I want you to stay by me.
Please. Let's stay by each other forever.
That's exactly why I have to go...
...so that we can be together forever.
Tomoya-kun, do you have everything you need?
Yeah, I've got 'em.
Shio-chan. Say "goodbye".
I'll be going now.
Have a good day.
Sanae-san is with Nagisa during the day.
The old man comes frequently, too.
Everyone's doing the best they can so Nagisa can deliver Ushio safely.
Nagisa, see you tomorrow.
Yes, see you tomorrow.
At times, I'm scared that you hate me.
If Nagisa hadn't met me, she wouldn't have to go through this life or death delivery.
I changed Nagisa.
When I first met her, she looked really weak.
So weak it made me think she would've stayed standing at the foot of the hill if I hadn't spoken.
I was giving myself too much credit.
I thought she became stronger because of me.
And I thought I became stronger because of her.
That's exactly right, Tomoya-san.
Both Akio-san and I are very grateful to you.
But I'm starting to question things.
If I weren't here, she would still be at your home,
and though she might have had less friends,
she would be living a happy life of her own.
If not, she might have met someone better than me and be having a happier life.
We can't imagine such a thing, Tomoya-san.
I knew you'd say that since you're a kind person.
But...
I mean it from my heart.
I'm sorry; I acted like a child there.
I continued to work.
A machine that flies.
I will make the machine that will take us from here.
Sign: Tonari-machi Hospital - lit. "Neighboring City Hospital"
It's almost Christmas.
And your birthday at the same time.
What do you want this year?
The Big Dango Family.
What's the point of collecting more of that?
Besides, you won't find them anywhere anymore.
Would it be hard to find?
It's probably impossible.
I see...
How did you find that?
Tomoya-kun went through lots of trouble to find it.
How does getting one every year sound?
You'll eventually get a real "big family".
The older ones will probably get jealous.
But I can't hug all three at once.
So I want you to hug them instead.
Me?
Here you go.
Tomoya-kun, you look adorable.
I can smell Nagisa on it.
Yo. Long time no see.
Who are you?
Hey! We went through this last April!
Sunohara-san. Happy New Year.
Hey, Nagisa-chan. Long time no see.
Whoa!!!
It gets this big, eh?
It's a little embarrassing.
Here.
This is almost mysterious.
That's enough!
Stop being so tactless.
You haven't changed even though
you've become a member of society.
Onee-chan, I don't think you can talk about others.
Kyou. Fujibayashi.
Thanks for coming.
Happy New Year.
I'm here, too.
I came back from America.
Happy New Year, everyone.
Kotomi-chan.
Happy New Year to you, too.
It's really big.
Yes.
May I touch?
Sure.
It's very wonderful.
Me! I'm up next!
Not you.
Why?
The rice cake!
So this is Tomoyo's family, eh?
Her brother looks well, too.
We have one from Miyazawa-san, too.
Looks like everyone is getting along well.
This one is from Nishina-san and Sugisaka-san.
They're saying to do your best to have a healthy baby.
Oh yeah.
Give this to Mei-chan.
What's this?
Yoshino-san's newest release.
He started singing again as an indie.
"Lobe and Spannier"?
You read that "Love and Spanner".
Did you really graduate from high school?
It's a very distinctive title.
Yoshino-san and I came up with the title.
We got it to sound as normal as we could.
Hey, Okazaki.
What?
Yes?
Hey, they're both Okazaki now.
Then, Okazaki-guy.
What kinda name is that?
What does it feel like to become a father?
What a strange thing to ask.
I'm interested in hearing your thoughts, too.
What does it feel like to become a parent?
I thought becoming a parent is something way in the future.
But hearing you two were going to be parents,
it suddenly felt much more "real".
I probably shouldn't say this in front of you two,
but no one becomes a father because they want to.
I consider it more like a natural hazard like earthquake or lightning.
So I want to know what's in your mind
as you become a father.
Beats me.
I don't have a clue.
Are you sure that's all right?
Honestly, I'm not sure if it registers that I'm going to be a father yet.
But, I found a person I can love, and this happened when I lived for her sake.
That's all there is to it.
In the end, Okazaki,
you haven't changed at all.
Yeah?
Yeah.
It felt like you and Nagisa-chan became distant, but you weren't so far away.
Glad I found that out.
Yeah. I was actually nervous until I saw you two.
It felt like you two were way ahead in the life game.
Life is very mysterious.
Where does it come from, and where does it go?
Right now, I'm researching the same thing my father and mother were.
The hidden world, was it?
Yup.
It's another world that exists right next to this one, but it can't be seen or felt.
But we're starting to find out that's not entirely true.
Really?
Yup.
It's probably akin to a warped extra dimension.
The current theory states that what we perceive as objects are stuck firm to high dimension planes...
...and they cannot remove themselves from their maximum existence.
But, for example, energy due to gravity is said to transcend through dimensions.
Just like that-
Stop!
Tell us the story so we can understand.
That was a very, very simplified explanation.
So you're saying that this world and the hidden world are related strongly at a deep level?
Yes.
Time, space, and people's minds echo in a strange way...
...to recreate both worlds or create whole new ones.
It might be affecting each other like that.
That's what I wanted to say.
Could our lives be tied to that world, too?
Maybe, then yet again maybe not.
This world is really filled with mystery.
I wonder what the hidden world is like.
What? Why did I just think of that play?
The girl in the world that ended.
Why did I know that story?
Tomoya-kun?
I was just thinking.
In that other world, people might be having parties like us.
There may be more than one hidden world.
There's a theory of multiple worlds existing, too.
Fujibayashi.
I remember you saying something like that when you were talking about fortune telling.
Yes. There is no one future,
but there are many possibilities.
I still think that.
Then there could be a world where one of you is dating me, right?
Not a chance with me.
I'd reject you, too!
I can't create anything.
All I can do is pile up the junk.
No matter how much effort I put in, it was useless.
I had stopped working at a certain point.
So you were here, too.
Old man.
The city will continue to change.
Nothing can stay as is.
That's what it means to live.
But isn't this an important place for you?
If I interfered with this construction, would Nagisa be able to stay well?
It's an idea that's crossed my mind.
Don't be ridiculous. It's a great thing for the people of this city for this hospital to be built.
It's not something we can mess with.
I'm coming to hate this city.
To tell you the truth, I asked people involved with the construction to preserve some trees.
Tomo-pyon did something similar, right?
Tomo-pyon?
Oh, you mean Tomoyo.
I heard you guys decided to deliver at a hospital.
Yeah. It's more reassuring to be in a place where there's equipment.
Walk over, wait, and pray, eh?
We might get some snow.
That night, we were buried with snow.
With neither trains nor cars able to move,
the city froze as if it had gotten sick.
Meanwhile, Nagisa caught a fever,
and the contractions started at the same time.
It was labor two weeks earlier than expected.
Nagisa! Hang in there, Nagisa!
Nagisa...
I'm all right...
I will give birth to Shio-chan.
I will live with you and Shio-chan. The three of us together.
Yagi-san's here.
The cars can't move yet.
Why did this come on a day like this?
Furukawa-san. Please prepare hot water.
As much as possible.
Okay.
Okazaki-san. You keep on supporting your wife.
It's all right to be holding on to her hand, right?
Of course. Please do.
Nagisa. I'm right here.
Don't lose, Nagisa!
You will give birth fine and start a new life, right?
With Ushio, a new life for the three of us.
Don't worry, calm down.
There now, breathe out.
Yes, that's right.
Breathe.
Yes, loosen up.
Yes, good. That's it.
Shall I take a look?
Nagisa passed out multiple times.
And she woke up to the pain.
It was so cruel that I wanted to stop looking.
It was long, and it felt like it was going to continue without end.
Even I felt as though I was going to pass out.
Perhaps, my mind couldn't take any more.
Or perhaps, I despaired over everything.
Nagisa?
Nagisa...
Nagisa!
Tomoya...kun...
I'm here! I'm right here!
You can hear it, right?
The voice of our child crying?
Yes...
Look. I'm the first one to hug her.
She's beautiful.
It's our child.
This is Ushio.
Shio-chan...
It's a girl! It's a lively girl!
Yes...
I'm glad I was able to have her at home.
Though, I made Shio-chan go through extra trouble.
Well done... You've done a great job.
But, I'm a little tired now.
May I rest for a while?
Nagisa!
Damn it! Is the doctor still not here?!
Cars still can't move?!
Nagisa... Hold on, Nagisa.
L-Let's talk for a little more.
You can just listen to me.
Look, it's our child.
She looks like a monkey, doesn't she?
So small, too.
I'm going to call to her now, okay?
Ushio.
I'm your daddy, Ushio.
She's your mommy.
Look.
She ignored me.
Yeah, of course. She doesn't understand what I'm saying.
I'm sure she'll grow fast, enter elementary school.
Then we'd go to the open house and sports day together.
We'll participate as a family.
I used to be the one that scoffed at stuff like that the most.
Nagisa?
Feel that? It's Ushio's cheek.
Yeah? Feel that?
Nagisa...
You said you'll always be with me, right?
You said you'll always be with me...
We... We promised we will, many times, right?
That's my dream.
"There's nothing good even if I lived."
"It's a boring life."
It's a dream a guy, who used to think things like that, finally found.
Hey... Nagisa.
Nagisa...
Nagisa!
Do you like this school?
I really, really love it.
But nothing can stay unchanged.
Fun things... Happy things...
They can't all possibly stay unchanged.
Even so, can you keep on loving this place?
If only we'd never met...
We should have taken different paths.
I wouldn't have dated Nagisa,
nor would I have married her.
Ushio wouldn't have been born, either.
Then this sadness would never have haunted me.
I should never have met her.