Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!
Are you worried?
REVIVAL
Ryuzaki, let me go.
Chief, I'll go with you.
All right,
but this is Kira.
Be careful when arresting him,
don't let him see your face.
Watari, if Higuchi makes
even the slightest move...
Yes. I'll stop him
without killing him.
Aizawa. Do you have something
to cover your face with?
Yes.
Cover me.
Yes. Thank you very much, Chief!
Higuchi, put your hands up
and get out of the car!
We've captured Higuchi!
Mr. Mogi, as planned,
give Higuchi a headset.
Yes.
Higuchi...
How do you kill people?
Tell me!
I'll use whatever means necessary
to make you speak
if you won't tell me.
The notebook.
Notebook?
You may not believe me,
but if I write the name of someone
whose face I know in that notebook,
that person dies.
A notebook...
Mr. Yagami.
Yeah, there's one
in Higuchi's bag.
He's written names in it,
but it looks like any
other notebook...
What's wrong, Mr. Yagami?
A monster!
Calm down.
You don't have a gun
on you right now.
Oh yeah...
Are you all right. Chief?
M- Mogi, can't you see that?!
Chief, you're probably tired.
What's wrong, Mr. Mogi?!
Oh... uh... I-It seems...
only people who've touched
this notebook can see this...
This monster...!
Please bring the notebook
to the helicopter.
Yes...
What in the world are
you planning, Light Yagami?
When you take hold of
the notebook once more,
all your memories of when you had
the Death Note will return.
But...
Ryuzaki, this is it.
It's a Shinigami... isn't it?
They... really... do... exist...
Light Yagami, a notebook...
Show each other our notebooks
in Aoyama...
- Love at first sight...
- Ryuzaki, let me see it, too!
The Second Kira...!
Two books!
There are more than
two notebooks in existence!
This isn't ﬁnished yet...
A Shinigami?
Write the name in the Death Note.
...and L.
lam L.
Are... Are you all right?
Anyone would be surprised
by that monster...
Ryuzaki.
Yes.
I'm going to try and match
the names written in here...
with the names
of the victims.
Huh? Yes...
Well... Of course.
I've won!
It's just as I planned.
I relinquish ownership
of this notebook.
Now the ownership of
the notebook has returned to you, Rem.
Am I right?
That's right.
You're being persistent.
Then, give that notebook to Ryuk.
What?
Fine.
Now ownership of
that notebook belongs to Ryuk.
Ryuk, drop that notebook on the ground
of the Human World again.
Huh? Well, okay.
Now ownership of
this notebook belongs to me again.
Hold on, it's just gone around.
Nothing's changed.
Yeah, that may be true.
But there will come a time
when this will be useful.
This notebook,
the one I first received...
I'm now going to return it
to you, Ryuk.
Give it back to Rem.
Here.
Rem, give that to a person
with some status and
a strong desire for power,
who'll probably use the notebook
only for his own personal gain.
Misa will be released from
her confinement if you do that.
If she is not released
after several years, kill me.
How does that sound?
Light Yagami,
what are you thinking?
This is to save Misa.
Trust me.
All right. If Misa will be saved
I'll do as you ask.
Later, I'll make sure
to be confined like Misa
and put under 24-hour surveillance.
While in confinement, I will
relinquish ownership of the notebook,
and lose all memory of
the Death Note.
During that time, the killings
of criminals will begin again.
If that continues,
Ryuzaki will have to release
the both of us sooner or later.
Since I've lost all my memory,
I'll probably try to catch Kira...
Since that's
the kind of person I am.
And you'll try to catch the guy
who Rem gives the notebook to
and steal the notebook
before L gets to him.
That's right.
And at that time, I'll kill
the owner of the notebook.
But there is one problem...
If you don't have ownership
of the notebook,
your memory will only return
while you're touching the notebook.
Once you let go, your memory
will disappear.
I'll kill Higuchi without
letting go of this notebook!
If I do that, ownership will
transfer back to me and...
my memory won't disappear!
I have to pull here four times
within a second...
All right...
I was wearing this watch.
Habits don't change.
Mr. Yagami, take Higuchi
to the car.
All right! Understood!
KYOSUKE HIGUCHI
This notebook...
What do you suppose we'll find
if we have it scientifically analyzed?
That's not like you.
That thing is beyond science.
That's true...
This is the longest forty
seconds of my life...
Higuchi?!
Ryuzaki, Higuchi is...!
W What?!
hat 8 going on?!
Hey, Higuchi!
What are you doing, Dad?!
If Higuchi dies, now...
Impossible!
No, but, he's already...
Yeah, he's dead.
Ryuzaki...
you're next.
How to use it...
The human whose name
is written in this note shall... die.
This note will not take effect unless
the writer has the person's face in
their mind when writing his/her name.
Therefore, people sharing
the same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death
is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written...
in the next 6 minutes and 40 seconds.
Additionally...
on the back cover's instructions...
If you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the humans who have touched
the note until then will die.
What?!
Is that true, Aizawa?!
- Yeah, that's what's written.
- That's right. With a rule like that,
- No way! Why didn't you tell me before?
- Father and the others
- How was I supposed to know?!
- won't try to dispose of it
and I won't lose my memory of this.
Rem, there's no way that
the old man will get mad at us
if we write a fake rule
here, will he?
No. There are no such
rules against doing so.
Fine then.
Light, you owe me apples.
Man, I shouldn't have
touched it just
because I wanted
to see the Shinigami.
Then you'd be the only one
who wouldn't know what was
going on in the investigation.
Would you be okay with that?
No, I want to work on the same terms
as everyone else. Yes.
And...
this last sentence...
If the person using
the note fails to...
consecutively write names
of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other...
Then the user,
will die.
What? Which means that...
Light and Misa-Misa are
completely cleared!
Yes, indeed...
Light and Amane were detained
for more than fifty days
and are still under surveillance.
There's no way they'd still be
alive if they're both Kira.
Aren't you glad, Chief?!
Yeah.
Rem...
...was it?
You, the white-colored Shinigami.
Ryuzaki! That's rude!
Referring to it by it's skin color...
Yes, it is...
There are other notebooks in
the Human World, aren't there?
Who knows? There may be.
There may not be.
If there were other notebooks,
are all their rules the same?
It's useless, Ryuzaki...
You can't break this rule with Rem.
Yeah, they're the same.
There are many notebooks
in the Shinigami Realm,
but their rules are all the same.
Even the rules for when
humans obtain them.
Ryuzaki...
Light and Amane are cleared now.
Their surveillance is over.
That's right. It's already clear.
You're right...
I understand.
I'm very sorry about everything
that's happened until now.
Thank goodness...
Yeah, but we still can't say
that we've solved the case.
I want these handcuffs removed,
but can I continue to
investigate here?
Yes...
Misa and I are now
completely cleared...
He has no choice but to believe
the fake rule that was written
by a Shinigami into
the notebook of death...
With the fake rules that I made up...
Ryuzaki's lost his edge.
Listen, Ryuzaki...
In any world, rules are always
created by those who are gods.
You will be beaten by
the rule I have created
and for the crime of
defying the god of the new world...
you are going to die.
Light!
Send me text messages
every day.
We're finally saying good-bye
to Misa-Misa...
Hey, Matsuda,
leave those two alone!
See you later, Misa-Misa!
Hey.
The surveillance cameras
can't see my mouth at this angle.
Misa, I'm going to tell you
about a certain place.
I want you to dig up something
when no one is watching.
Light, your memory has returned!
Don't worry,
Misa will do a good job!
Light, I remember.
I remember everything that happened
when I had this notebook.
You buried this notebook
so I could remember...
FOR MISA, LIGHT YAGAMI
Misa, by the time you read this letter,
you should have remembered everything.
A letter from Light!
Do you remember my friend
at To-oh University
who went by
the name Hideki Ryuga?
I want you to write his name
in the notebook... and kill him.
Also, burn this letter,
hide a few pages of the notebook
with you, and bury the notebook.
When you meet me again,
casually touch me with
a piece of the notebook.
If you do this, Misa Amane, I will...
- love you for the rest of my life.
- "love you for the rest of my life. "
All right!
I see. This is Light's plan!
He wanted me to get
this notebook,
regain my memory...
And kill Hideki Ryuga... Ryuzaki...
One of Light's obstacles will disappear
and I'll be helpful to him.
It's no good... Light...
I can't remember his name...
I saw dozens and hundreds of
names and life spans... every day.
I can't remember at all!
Misa's so stupid!
I'm finally able to come back!
Ryuk!
It's been a while...
How have you been?
Sorry, but...
I'm a male. You're making me shy.
Oh yeah...
Here.
Light told me to bring this.
Is it really that delicious?
Yeah. Apples in the Human World are...
what's the word, juicy?
At any rate, they're great.
Do you want to eat one?
It's an apple from
the Shinigami Realm.
It doesn't look very good...
Come on, just one bite.
Oh yeah, Ryuk...
Do the eye deal with me.
Sand!
A deal, huh?
You understand, don't you?
You've made a deal with
Rem once before.
Do you really want to halve
your life a second time?
Hmm... Well, that can't be helped...
I've forgotten the name
I had to remember...
Light will be angry with me
if I don't take a look at it again...
Well, it's fine with me...
Oh, it's Misa-Misa.
The poor thing.
We can't turn on
our cell phones here,
so she has to
come here to visit you.
Light, go to her quickly.
You shouldn't make
a woman wait.
Yeah.
Ryuk!
Why is he attached to Misa?
Misa's life has been halved
once more!
No way... Did she...
do the eye deal with Ryuk?!
Light...
It's been a while, Ryuk.
Light, I'm sorry.
I don't remember
Hideki Ryuga's name.
I just can't remember.
I see. That's too bad.
But I did the eye bargain with Ryuk!
Everything is going
exactly as planned... huh?
Idiot! If you do that,
your life will...!
No, it's all right.
I want to be of help to you...
Misa, right now,
I want to live with you for a long time
in an ideal world.
That's how I feel.
Light, I'm so happy!
Misa...
Let's make a new world without crime...
a world with only kind people...
Let's make it together.
TO BE CONTINUED
This single page Forever depressing
A ﬂeeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control"
they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
PREVIEW
Goodbye.