Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I gotta pee!
I've heard that newspaper can be used as a substitute.
Number onesies go here.
What's this?
Huh? Huh?
I can play!
Huh?
This isn't a place to play.
It's the toilet.
To-i-let.
Oh!
That's right!
This is the toilet, okay?
This is a nice bed!
Eh?!
Well, these things take patience.
I-I gotta pee!
I'm gonna pee myself!
Where should I go?
Huh?
I peed properly!
Hey!
And on the laundry I just washed...
Mom!
What is it?
Pee.
Pee?
If you need to pee, then go to the toilet.
I wet myself.
You shouldn't do that, right?
You should go to the toilet before it comes out.
Oh dear me!
You shouldn't do that, right?
If you go pee, you gotta cover it with sand!