Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Those cats definitely came this way.
Chi?
I finally hit my mark.
I need to restate firmly that pets aren't allowed here.
Geez, thanks to that black bear cat, it's come to this.
I wonder if Chi's up there.
Huh?
Where is this?
Hey!
That surprised me!
This is my house.
House?
Chi will be going home!
Eh?
Chi's not here.
I guess it was down after all.
Huh?
Okay, okay.
Oh hi, landlady.
Greetings.
I have an inquiry, but...
Are you keeping a cat?
A cat? Yes, I'm keeping one.
I knew you were keeping one.
There's been a lot of cat damage,
and as you can see, they're forbidden in the apartment lease.
Forbidden?
We're going home.
Keep quiet and follow me.
Okay!
This way.
We're jumping.
Jump!
No way!