Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Mom, let's play!
Come on, Chi.
Don't get in the way.
What's that?!
Hey, Chi!
You shouldn't do that.
Chi, don't get in the way, okay?
Dad, let's play!
Hey, Chi!
I'm sorry, Chi.
I'll be finished with work soon, so wait for me, all right?
Chi!
Youhei!
Let's play!
Pee is leaking!
Note: "Chi" is "pee" in Japanese.
Nobody cares about me.
Chi.
I'm done with work!
Dad!
Now then, come here, Chi.
We're gonna play, right?
Chi.
Good girl.
Ah! I'm going to play with Chi too!
Youhei!
That's a cute way of lying down.
Mom!
Everyone is getting together.
Let's play, everyone!
I like Chi's tail.
The end of the tail's a bit thinner, and
it's all fluffy!
For me, it has to be the pads of her paws.
If you press, it's like jelly,
and it feels great.
That's true.
Also...
if you press it, her claws come out.
The mechanism is amazing.
Chi?
She doesn't like too little attention, but...
...she doesn't like too much attention either.