Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I wonder if Youhei will be lonely?
Yeah, it's understandable.
He's been playing happily with Chi.
Let's play?
Hey, let's play!
He's not playing.
Chi seems lonely too.
Maybe it realizes something?
Let's play!
Hey, let's play!
Chi, you'll be going away, huh?
What?
No! No!
I don't like being squeezed!
Let go of me!
Chi...
Ow!
She'll be mad at me!
Huh?
She isn't getting mad.
Chi...
But, there's no helping it, is there?
Dogs and cats are prohibited here...
Chi will be able to live more comfortably somewhere else.
Yeah.
I'm sure Chi will be happier that way.
What's the matter?
What? What?
Huh?
Hello, Yamada residence.
Ah, yes.
No, thank you too.
Umm, about that...
I'm sorry!
Eh?
My husband brought a kitten home from work today.
It was from his superior, so there was no way he could turn it down.
Then, what about Chi?
What?
I'm truly sorry.
We can't take Chi-chan in anymore.
Really?!
Don't worry about it!
Please, don't worry about it!
What? What's going on?
Okay, well then, good night.
Dad!
Yeah, let's keep it here.
Hey, is that about Chi?
Chi can stay here?
That's right.
Yeah. Chi will become our kitty.
I feel like this is fate now.
It's actually something we shouldn't do, but...
Chi.
No! No!
Chi!
Let's play?