Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I'm stuffed.
It's been a while since we've all gone out.
That's right.
The weather is good too. Isn't that great?
Huh?
What's wrong?
I was just wondering whether Chi will really be okay house-sitting all alone.
She'll be fine.
We arranged everything carefully.
That's right.
Well then, let's go.
Huh?
What is it?
Did we close the door to the bathroom?
It would be dangerous if Chi fell into the bath.
That's true.
But it should be closed.
Hmm, sorry.
I'm going to check.
What a worrywart.
All right.
Chi.
Be a good girl and wait.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It was all right.
Now then, shall we go?
Yeah!
Huh?
Did we remove the hot water from the electric kettle?
Oh! Did we put the knives away?
We did it all properly.
Hmm...
I'm going to check-
Dad!
I'm worried!
What's this?
What's this?!
They'll get mad at me!
Run away!
Huh?
Everyone's gone out.
There's nobody here!
Yay! They won't get mad at me!
They won't get mad at me, no matter what I do!
They won't get mad at all!
This is fun!