Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Thanks for the food!
This is yummy.
We're having quite a dinner tonight.
Youhei, what's that?
This?
It's a spoon.
It smells good!
Only smell?
This egg custard is also yummy.
Thank you.
Eh?
This?
Does it taste good?
I'll give you only a bit.
Yummy!
Chi.
How about this?
It tastes good.
There.
Yummy!
There's a lot...
of yummy food up there!
This tastes good too.
Yummy!
Really?
Thank you.
Please make it again.
Okay.
Does she still want something?
I wonder if we gave her too much.
Is it bad to give food to Chi?
Some things that people eat aren't good for cats.
Yummy things.
No, no.
I want yummy things too!
Oh, I have an idea.
There you go, Chi.
Here's your meal.
It's yummy things!
It's what I normally feed her.
Yummy things are really yummy!