Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gotta pee!
Where should I go?
Where should I go?!
It got me again!
Kitty leaked pee!
What?
What? What?
Hey!
Ah, that startled me.
What is she barking about?
I'm home!
Kitty is peeing here and there?
Just when I thought Youhei's problems with the toilet were decreasing...
Now we have to worry about training the kitty.
Is that so?
This fellow is a baby after all.
I wonder if we should buy actual kitty litter?
Of course, it's just until we can find a new owner for it...
Ooh, gotta pee.
Where? Where? Where should I go?
Can't we get through somehow with the shredded newspaper?
But, it's done it so many times today.
Even in the laundry that I'd washed and dried.
Well, but a kitty wouldn't know about things like laundry.
The laundry was left out over there, so it can't be helped.
Do you have to put it like that?
Eh?
B-But it's true, right?
Hold on a second, Dad...
Pee!
Hmm?
Eh?
What's wrong?
You can go to the toilet by yourself, right, Youhei?
Pee!
Eh?
M-My favorite bag...
I-It got me...
Cover with sand!
It was left out over there, so it can't be helped, right?
All right!
I'm going to buy kitty litter, right now!
Eh?
Right now?
I peed properly!