Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Dad! Dad!
An amazing cat came into the house!
An amazing cat?
It was jet black and this big!
It was huge!
It was a scary cat like this.
It swaggered and gave us a sharp stare.
It must be the "big cat" that's been causing problems in the apartment complex.
It's been appearing frequently in homes around here.
It would be good if they don't find Chi as well.
Youhei was a real problem!
Chi was in trouble, and I did my best!
Chi, dinner time.
I overfilled it.
Oh, well.
That's a lot!
If she's full, she'll leave it.
Let's eat-
It knocked over three flower pots?
Yes, according to rumors.
That cat has fast legs.
What a bother.
What should I do?
Nobody is here.
That's a scary face!
But...
If Chi doesn't do it...
Don't come in our home!
I've been stepped on!
I'll be crushed!
Huh?
I wasn't stepped on.
Chi's dinner!
Don't eat it! Don't eat it!
Chi's dinner...