Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Yay!
Wait, wait!
Oh! Looks like you're having fun.
It's the landlady.
Huh?
Yamada-san?
Yes.
Dad, please take care of her!
Yamada-san.
It's me, the landlady.
Yes. Good afternoon.
Is the Yamada family having any problems?
Let me go!
N-No. We're not having any...
How could we be having problems?
If that's the case, it's fine.
Oh my! Sorry to interrupt your teatime.
Oh! This is just... I was in a panic...
In a panic?
No, I mean...
"Tea. Would you like some tea?" That's what I was thinking...
Oh! Thank you.
Then let's talk inside.
Thanks for inviting me.
We have to hide Chi's toys.
Youhei, please help.
Okay.
I'll play too.
Oh, Chi's fur...
Umm... Now is a bit...
It's a bit untidy...
I don't mind.
It's very tidy.
W-Welcome.
Good afternoon, madam.
Thanks for inviting me.
Please sit here.
Thank you.
Please, please.
Really, thank you for inviting me.
N-No problem.
No problem...
Chi, let's wait here patiently, okay?
Youhei, are we going to play here?