Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Huh?
Youhei. Well done!
Now, Chi, let's go to the vet.
Let me out.
Let me out! Let me out of here!
Chi.
Have a nice trip.
Vaccinations prevent you from getting sick.
That's right.
It's for you, Chi.
Put up with the injection.
Traitors!
I thought you were my comrades.
Yamada Chi-chan.
So you came to have a combo vaccination, right?
Is it all right that she's in a net?
Oh, it doesn't matter how she's held.
Especially for the ones that get frantic.
Now, you're a good girl.
This isn't going to hurt.
What are you going to do?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
How was Chi?
I get exhausted every time I take her to the vet.
Hey!
What's up?
I've run away from home.
They were cruel to me!
I thought they were my comrades.
You shouldn't trust them.
Huh?
Trust?
Yeah.
You shouldn't trust humans too much.
Yes. Yes.
Shouldn't trust!
Yeah.
Trust?
What's trust?
Hey, come on.