Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Mom, what's wrong?
Youhei is feeling better, but now Mom has a fever.
Are you all right?
I'll be better after I sleep.
I have to go out for a while,
but I'll come back early and prepare dinner.
Thank you.
What's going on, everyone?
Well, I have to go to work,
so watch the house.
Okay.
Youhei, isn't this fun?
Hush.
What's wrong, Youhei?
I wonder if Mom is all right.
Oh! I have to change the sheet.
Youhei, what are you going to do?
No, I can't reach it.
This will do it.
More...
Youhei, you're big.
Huh?
What's this.
Oh! It's cold.
Yay!
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Yes.
Youhei, that's dangerous.
Because I...
What were you...
Youhei.
You did that for me?
Sorry.
Youhei.
Thanks.
Mom.
I'm home.
Oh!
All three sleeping together, eh?
I envy that.