Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Huh? A notice?
Yes.
A while ago, the landlady posted a notice that said, "Inform me if you see a cat."
We're in trouble.
Anyway, we have to be more careful, so Chi won't be discovered.
Right.
It'll cause trouble if we let her go outside and get captured.
A stroll.
We have to be careful when we leave via the front door.
And windows too.
We mustn't leave the windows open.
Chi!
Wait!
Youhei, catch her!
Huh?
Let me go!
That was close.
We left the screen door open while
discussing keeping the windows shut.
I'm going outside to play!
I wonder when we left it open.
I think I closed it after I went out to hang the laundry up to dry.
I closed it too.
That's weird.
I wonder how it got open.
Chi.
So she opened it herself.
She's clever.
Yes, she is.
So, she wants to go out again.
Wait!
No, I'm going!
It's amazing that she opened the screen door by herself.
I assume she can't open the glass door,
but if that's closed, we won't get any fresh air.
Huh?
Chi, you can't go out whenever you want.
We're safe with this now.
I suppose so.
It doesn't open.
Why?