Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi?
She's not here.
What should I do...
if the landlady finds her or something?
What will happen if she's found?
I wonder what will happen...
Who are you?
C-Catch it!
O-Okay!
Run!
Do you want some?
I caught it.
There!
Parent and child?
And here I thought there was just one.
I see there are two rampaging around.
What are you doing?!
We're running! Follow me!
Okay!
They got away!
Wait!
Where in the world did Chi go?
Ah! Chi!
Huh?
The black bear cat...
Chi!
Huh?
Wait!
Hey!
L-Landlady?!
Wait! Hey! Cats! Wait!
Hey!
Wait!
What will happen if Chi gets caught?
I wonder what will happen...
We're climbing.
Huh?
I can't take it. I can't climb!
I'm going home!
That's impossible now.
Follow me!
Why? I don't wanna!
My instincts are telling me to run.
In-stink-s?
Chi doesn't know in-stinks.
I've never met him!
It's an important thing.
Run!
What, what?!