Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Umm...
Are the cups cleared away?
I wonder if I locked up properly so that she can't get out.
What are you doing, everyone?
Oh yes!
I have to check there.
What? What?
Kitty litter, okay.
Mom.
What should I do?
Well...
You can put away the toys, okay?
Okay!
Chi!
Thank you, Chi.
Huh?
You're not playing?
Prey!
This is fun!
Now, now, Chi.
Chi, you shouldn't intrude.
Chi, I'm putting things away so you won't get tangled up while you're in the house alone.
All right.
With this, preparations are complete.
Boring...
Oops!
I forgot Chi's dinner.
I can eat this much?!
Let's eat!
Chi is house-sitting, so I've given her a bit more than usual.
Hey.
If we're going out, now's the time.
I see.
Yummy!
Well then, off we go!
Going out!
But will Chi be okay house-sitting on her own?
She'll be fine.
That's right.
It's not like Chi will get lonely when she's all alone.
I'm not worried at...
Chi!
Dad!
Goodness me.
You were the one who said we should let her house-sit, right, Dad?
Eh? Ah... Is that so?
That's right!
But Chi will be...
That's not an excuse.
Let's go.
I'm stuffed!