Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This is bad.
And the deadline was yesterday...
Arg!
This is completely hopeless!
I can't come up with anything!
Is Dad trying to catch up again?
Hmm?
Yeah.
It seems he's busy with work.
Umm...
Gra... Gra...
Graphic designer.
I'll read a picture book to you today, so be quiet, okay?
Okay!
Dad, let's play!
Hey! Hey!
I'm going to the toilet.
Dad, this is cool!
It must be nice to be carefree like a cat...
You're not playing?
Huh?
What's that up there?
There's loads of stuff!
This is fun!
There's lots of things to play with.
H-Hey, Chi!
You can't do that!
No! I want to play more!
I want to play more!
Ah... It's done this much...
Even though I bought toys for Chi to play with...
Why my work tools?
This is...
That's it!
If I use "sky" as the motif...
It will work!
I can visualize the idea!
...and they all stayed together.
You did very well, Chi!
Amazing!
They all lived happily ever after.
Now then, let's do this!
I wonder if Dad is playing with Chi.
Who knows?
There are lots of things to play with in Dad's room!
All right, let's do our best, Chi!
Oh...
That looks fun.