Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The strange cat came again!
It ate all of Chi's dinner!
She seems pretty lively today.
She sure is.
Even though I gave her this much dry food,
she ate all of it.
Oh?
There was only Chi at home, so I did my best!
To be able to eat that much...
You're pretty amazing, Chi.
Did you understand, Dad?
I see.
It was that delicious?
Dinner's ready.
Let's eat!
I'm starving!
Huh?
Chi doesn't have any dinner!
What about Chi's dinner?
She isn't having any.
Since she ate so much at lunch.
We don't want to upset her stomach.
That reminds me.
That big cat seems to break flower pots and steal sliced salmon.
Eh? That's amazing.
What kind of cat was it?
I didn't have lunch!
It had a face like that.
It was black, short, and stout.
The stranger came swaggering in.
It had scary eyes.
It walked slowly.
It stared sharply.
It scared me.
And it crunched Chi's dinner!
And it's huge!
Got it?
Sort of...
As I thought, it's hard to understand without seeing the real thing.
That's it!
This is it!
A cat like this one!
Eh?!
That's him!
A bear?!
A bit different, but you get the idea.
Do you get it, Dad?
Dad, do you get it?
Yeah, I've got it.
Isn't that great, Youhei.
Yay!
Huh?
What about Chi's dinner?