Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The next station is my home.
My home.
My home?
That's a nice station.
Hmm?
Departing!
What's that?
That's weird!
Trying to catch the moon...
That's it!
Youhei has so many toys, yet Chi has none...
Huh?
It disappeared.
Where did it run away to?
I'm going out for a while.
Eh?
A business meeting?
Nope. Just a bit of shopping.
Oh...
Have a safe trip.
Umm, excuse me.
Yes?
Ah! The customer from before.
Ah, hi.
Where are cat toys?
Oh my, this time it's kitty toys?
Here! Right this way!
This way!
Over here we have a wide range of popular toys for all kinds of cats, from kittens to calm adults.
The ever-popular floundering fish!
The unmistakably pleasing fluttering hamster!
The ringing cat ball will fascinate them as they chase it!
The ribbon-tail will make them frolic mindlessly!
Your cat will chase caterpillar Poyonsuke at full speed!
We have lots of others too.
What were you looking for today?
Umm...
This one and... this one and...
Look Chi, toys!
Are you having fun, Chi?
I'm glad.
Sir?
Oh, yes?
Which would you like?
Umm...
A-All of them, please.
Okay!
Thank you very much!
Chi, there's a fun time ahead of you!