Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Homemade meals for cats?
I was thinking of making this for Chi.
Look at this.
It says that it's also good for her health.
It sounds interesting.
What are you doing?
Oh, Chi.
You'd like a nice meal too, right?
Huh?
When you finish, bring them over here.
This is quite a lot of work.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Chi, it will be ready soon.
Oh! Are you impatient for it?
I can't see it.
I wonder if it has boiled.
Huh?
Is it yummy?
I'm finally finished.
Gimme!
Now, Chi!
Wait!
Chi!
Gimme, gimme.
Now!
Hey, gimme!
What are you doing?
Hey, Chi!
Chi, wait!
Gimme, gimme.
We were making Chi's meal.
Could you help us?
Could you take care of Chi till we finish making it?
Okay.
It's done.
There, Chi.
Sorry for making you wait.
Huh?
What's this?
It smells good!
It's hot!
Oh! We forgot to cool it down.
Yes! Cats won't eat or drink hot things.
Sorry, Chi.
She's angry.
Sorry.