Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Kitty!
Nyanko?
Nameless kitty!
Hey, should we give it a name?
No, no.
It's not like we'll keep it.
Found you!
Pee?
Eh?
I'm busy at the moment.
Mom!
Kitty's peeing in the box!
Oh my!
I'm going to go pee too!
Is that so?
You peed in the litter box, eh?
That's a good kitty!
Ah, that's right!
Chi?
Here you go.
Milk!
Mom! Mom!
I peed properly too!
I didn't leak!
Oh! That's great!
I peed!
Chi?
Dad! Dad!
I didn't leak pee!
I peed properly!
Chi?
Very good, that's great, Youhei.
What's "chi"?
Ah-ha!
Now then, what's this?
Giving away a cute kitten.
Due to current circumstances, I'm no longer able to keep it.
What's this?!
They're all "Please take"!
Pee!
You called?
Hmm?
Chi?
You did  call!
Chi!
Just as I thought.
Note: In Japanese, "chi" means "pee".
Chi.
What is it?
See.
It seems to think "Chi" is its name.
Its name's been decided!