Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So different from the picture!
She's cute!
Wh-Who is this?!
Chi!
Who are you?!
Wait, wait!
Chi!
Juri!
Stay away!
Same as the picture!
Ah, Juri-chan!
Kitty, hug me!
What are you doing?!
Chi, calm down!
Kitty, hug!
Juri-chan, you stop too!
Come, come, come!
Hey Chi, come here already!
Come, come, come, Chi!
Cut it out, Juri!
Come here, Chi!
Juri-chan, juice.
Yay, juice!
Thanks, ma'am!
Juri-chan, do you like cats too?
Yeah!
After seeing the picture you sent us,
she's been really looking forward to meeting Chi-chan, right?
Yeah!
Huh?
What's this?
Hmm?
Chi, what's the matter?
A smell I don't know...
a suspicious smell.
I caught you!
Don't squeeze my tail!
So, do you understand?!
I can't let my guard down.
Ears!
What are you doing?!
I won't lose!
There! There! There! There! There!
There! There! There! There!
What?
Jump! Jump! Jump!
Jump up and down!
Isn't she angry?
Huh?
Chi's small, but she sure can go on a rampage, huh?
Just like Juri-chan...
What, what? What's with her?