Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Comb, comb!
Huh?
There, Chi.
Dad, this isn't what I want.
There you go.
This is fun!
There.
Oh, is that so?
It's a game!
So you want to play.
This is fun.
This isn't it.
Comb, comb!
What, have you already lost interest?
Mom, Mom.
What?
Listen, listen.
Chi is being funny.
What's funny?
She's following Dad all the time.
Following Dad?
Yes.
There you go.
See.
Oh!
She's following him again.
It's true.
Comb, comb, Dad!
I wonder what happened to Chi.
She's finally attracted to me.
No.
Huh?
Oh!
Dad, here!
That's it!
She seems to like the brush rather than Dad.
I see.
Chi is turning her back.
She seems to be waiting.
Comb, comb.
Comb.
Comb, comb...
Comb, comb.
My arm got tired.
So she's finally satisfied.
This side too.
You want me to brush your right side this time, eh?
Comb, comb feels nice!