Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So are you telling me to give Chi away?
I didn't say that.
Because that bear cat has been causing trouble, the landlady came here.
Chi hasn't been seen yet.
But...
Hey, hey. Do you want to play?
Chi.
That's distracting.
Chi, what are you doing?
What do you want to play with?
Hey, I think we can only hide Chi for so long.
Then, are we going to find a new owner?
Chatting?
Because we may be forced to move away from here.
I want to play!
But Chi is already part of our family.
What do you want to play with?
That's why I asked you, "What should we do?"
But what can we do?
Do you wanna play with me?
Hey, hey.
We've gotten out of sync.
Yeah.
Youhei.
Would you take care of Chi?
In the end, what do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
Oi!
This is hide and seek!
What are you doing, Chi?
Peek-A-
Boo!
She's distracting us so much that we can't talk.
We're talking about her anyway.
Anyway, Chi hasn't been found yet.
Yeah.
Let's think about this calmly.
About what we should do from now on.
Boo!
Peek-A-
Chi, I can't read my book.
Boo!