Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I peed properly!
Chi is really good!
That's right.
Nobody's here.
Thanks for the food!
Oh! Today you managed to eat without spilling any.
Very good, Youhei.
They'll come home, right?
Welcome home!
Thanks for your continued patronage!
Good work!
They'll come home, right?
What if...
When they get back, I'll be mad at them!
I wonder if Chi will be happy with the souvenir.
I wonder what she's doing now.
I'm sure she's feeling lonely.
Chi was alone all day.
Ah, Yamada-san.
Are you just returning now?
Good evening!
G-Good evening...
Oh...
She's sleeping.
Even though we hurried home because we were worried.
You did well house-sitting on your own, Chi.
Ah! The sofa is...!
Ah! The vase is...!
The curtains are...!
The tissues are...!
The cushion is...!
Dad, give me a hand with the cleaning.
Mom, give me a hand over here too.
Aw, the couch is totally soaked!
Dad, bring the soap over, right away!
Welcome home!