Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It was a nice bed, but...
Bye bye.
I'm going back home!
Huh?
What? What? What?
Wh-Wh-What?!
No no no no no no no!
LET GO OF ME!
Okay, okay.
Eh?
Huh?
Okay, I'm gonna make you all pretty!
Right then, here we go!
Help!
Don't run away!
Nooooo!
H-H-H-Hey!
Hey, get a grip.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Save me!
Help me!
Get ready!
I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna be killed!
Save me!
Ouch!
That was a tough time!
Okay then, next.
Washing a cat is quite a chore.
Even though both the bath and dryer feel great...
I thought I was going to die.
I'm so glad I didn't die.
It's become really pretty.
That's true!
Hey, hey, look!
Its back is this fluffy.
That's true!
Isn't that great?
So pretty.
It's sparkling!
Isn't it?
Soft!