Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This is great.
There, that's it for now.
I have work to do, so that's it for today.
M-More!
This is amazing.
I can make a blanket with this, Chi.
Youhei, what are you doing?
This a secret between you and me.
There, it's your fur ball.
What's this?
It smells like me!
Yay!
Stop it, Chi.
It's going to break.
It's mine! It's mine!
It'll be safe this way.
Youhei, it's not good to keep it to yourself.
What's this?
Oh?
Did Youhei do this?
Yeah.
It's like a ball.
Isn't it great?
What? What?
He made it with Chi's fur.
But, when did you make it?
It's really well made.
Eh?
Chi...
You're ruining all my efforts.
It's going to be a tough work to clean that up.
Yay!
This is fun!