Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's open!
Yay!
I can see outside!
Eh?
The big cat from before was here?
That's right.
Apparently it was in the window.
My, how careless.
Having it in such an easy place to find.
No, I mean,
I wonder who's keeping it?
Indeed.
Huh?
Is something up?
In your window...
In the window?
There's a small cat!
Eh?
There's a small cat there.
N-No way.
Aren't you mistaken?
Because we're not allowed to keep cats here.
There's no mistake.
In the bay window.
Look, there's a small cat.
A small cat...
A cat... A cat...
In the bay window, a small cat...
Oh my, look closer!
Oh my!
It's a stuffed toy!
So it is! It's a stuffed toy!
My mistake.
A stuffed toy...
Youhei, I need to do some work,
so go play with Chi.
Okay!
Chi, you shouldn't chew on that.
What's...
Ah!
It was an impulse buy.
Well, it's cute because it sort of looks like Chi.
Are you angry that I bought it on impulse?
Well done!
Eh?
Oh my, it's looking busy.
Sure is.
I've camouflaged her!
Isn't that great, Chi?
It's gotten really fancy.
Even though it's my workroom.