Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Youhei, let's play!
Chi, let's play!
What's this?
Chi, these are new building blocks.
Let's make a secret base.
What?
Chi, it's fun, isn't it?
Huh?
Never mind.
This is fun!
Look, look, Chi! This is great.
Youhei, this is fun!
He doesn't see this is fun.
Youhei. Look, look! This is fun.
Look, look! Chi.
Look, it's this tall.
Hey, hey, Youhei.
I can go round and round this much.
Round and round.
Oh my, oh my.
You really messed up the room.
After you tidy up, it's time for your snack.
Yes.
I wonder what today's snack will be.
This is nice.
Chi, don't go in there.
I will!
Chi! No!
What are you doing?
Youhei, it's ready.
Oh my, oh my.
Chi, this is fun, isn't it?
This is fun!