Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Juri-chan sure is energetic.
She was brought up in Hokkaido, after all.
Hey, this is a horse.
Ah, Chi.
Huh?
Chi, come here.
Chi?
What should we play this time?
What?
You want me to play with you?
Oh.
It looks like Chi's taken a liking to Juri-chan.
Chi! Let's play!
Chi, wait a minute.
What, what?
All right!
Chi, here we go!
There!
Yay!
I got it!
Chi! Bring it back!
Bring it back!
Gee, a dog would've brought it back.
There!
Yay!
This time, bring it back!
I got it!
Come on, you need to bring it back.
This time, bring it back.
There!
There we go.
Are you going for a walk?
Is it okay to keep a cat in this apartment?
Negative.
If something happens, we'll take her to our place.
Huh?
Thank you.
If something happens...
Chi would come to our place?
No, we were only talking about a worst case.
Bye-bye!
See you later.
We'll take her to our place.
Youhei!
Youhei! Let's play!
Chi, you won't go anywhere, right?
Chi...
Hey, hey, let's play!