Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We have to go today!
Yes! We must go!
Chi's...
health check-up!
What?
If we take it outside, there's a risk of being caught, but...
We have to go, for Chi's sake!
Huh?
Are we going on a picnic?
Not a picnic.
We're taking Chi to the the animal hospital.
The animal hospital?
We're going to see the doctor, to check whether Chi is okay.
So it's nothing like going to a real hospital.
What's this place?!
Now then, it's ready.
Huh?
Chi?
Are you in there?
Come on out.
Yay!
This is fun!
This is fun! This is fun!
What is this place?
Youhei, go get Chi.
Chi?
Youhei!
Youhei, let's play!
Huh?
Gotcha!
No! I want to play more!
Thank you, Youhei.
There.
Huh?
Make sure you're not discovered by the people in the apartment complex.
Yeah.
Especially by the landlady.
Well then, I'll be off.
What's this?
Right, all clear.
Left, all clear.
Okay, we're fine.
Be careful.
Chi, have a safe trip!
If they know Chi is here, we'll be forced to leave!
After all, we're really not allowed to keep a cat or dog in this apartment.
So don't speak so loudly.
Okay...
What's going on?
Th-That startled me.
That was close.
Will it be okay after this?