Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Well, nice, nice.
Huh?
Now that Mom's well.
Our house is totally back to normal.
Youhei, we have to leave soon.
Okay.
I'm going.
Yeah. Take care.
So now...
Chi.
What?
I haven't played with you for a while, so...
There, there, there.
There, there.
There.
Let's play a lot today.
It's a game!
Wait, wait!
There, there.
Yay.
Wait!
Are you enjoying this?
There!
Oh! Something is wrong.
I feel dizzy.
Is it...
fever?
I have a fever.
Dad, let's play some more.
Sorry, Chi.
What?
Although I was confident about my health.
Oh!
This isn't a toy.
What's this?
Chi!
Now, now.
Yay!
Gotcha!
Chi, give it back to me.
Oh!
It's a tug of war.
Tug, tug!
Chi, I have a fever.
Give it back to me.
This is fun!
Please.
Dad, you win.
I have a bad feeling.
What are we going to play with next?