Edited at https://subtitletools.com
What is this?
Stop...
Stop!
Not again...
Da...
Danger...
You...
What the hell?
Danger...
Hurry.
There will be a pillar of fire
where blind sheep gather
on holy ground.
The hour of Heaven's fall...
Hurry.
Go now...
Danger?
Wait, has something happened to Casca?
Epiphany
Snow, snow, flurry, flurry,
spirits of winter!
Drifting from the sky, spirits of winter!
Dancing as they fall, like puffs of down!
Try to catch them... How mysterious—
Spirits of winter...
Yay!
I caught something amazing!
Rickert!
I found a goblin—
Hey.
You've grown a bit, huh?
Rickert!
Welcome back, Erica.
Good work.
You've bulked up a bit.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Guts, you're alive?!
It's been two years!
Where and what were you—
Sorry, Rickert, but first,
is she...
Is Casca okay?
What's wrong?
Casca's...
Casca's gone.
Wh-What happened, Rickert?
Guts!
Why? Since when?
Where'd she go?!
It's all my fault!
It's my fault!
Because I took her with me to find nuts!
It happened about a month ago.
We had no choice.
After so long in the mine shafts,
Casca was in pretty bad shape.
She was barely eating.
Erica felt sorry for her, so...
Before I realized anything was
wrong, she was gone...
Rickert,
then why are you still here?
Why aren't you out looking for Casca?!
You know what state she's in!
You idiot!
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
What's with you?
You're the one who abandoned her
and were gone for two years!
You have no idea what Rickert went through!
He did go look for her a million times...
He could've just left.
But Rickert...
He came back.
He still came back here...
There's a reason I can't go.
Shut up...
I can't sleep.
Godo...
Is it a disease?
Nothing so fancy.
It's old age. Just old age.
I don't feel like listening to your prattle.
Show me your sword and false hand.
Chips in the edge, blood, rust, warp...
Looks like you've been
swinging this nonstop,
barely stopping for food or rest.
To survive, you can't afford sanity.
That's the kind of fighting you've been doing?
Two years ago,
when Rickert showed up at my door,
all of you grievously injured...
I still don't know what happened to you.
Given the monster that came after you,
I'm sure it was something abhorrent.
But vengeance and repaying blood debts?
Don't you think you're running away to battle?
To your hatred?
Hatred is where you turn when
you can't face your grief.
Vengeance is like sharpening a blood-stained,
rusty sword in a pool of blood.
The more you sharpen it, the more rust
builds up, so you sharpen it again.
Ultimately, all that remains is a
shattered pile of powdered rust.
You don't understand.
You can't understand.
Not here, where it's nice and cozy.
Not when you're about to kick the bucket,
acting like you have no unfinished business.
No one,
no human being,
can understand what happened.
They all died.
Every single one of them.
Without reason.
Without warning...
Without justice.
They died like vermin!
They died ignorant...
In that instant,
those who were irreplaceable to me...
To leave by yourself,
you cast aside those irreplaceable people.
Two years ago,
you went alone, leaving the remaining
irreplaceable people,
broken after unimaginable suffering.
You fled to be alone,
to use your personal hatred
to burn your very self.
Am I wrong?
You abandoned that girl.
Do you have the right to speak
of vengeance for your fallen?
When it really matters,
you lean on war for your actions.
You're an unsheathed sword,
whose blade has countless nicks.
It glistens with blood, encroached by rust.
A half-broken blade, with a lethal crack...
Hurry!
This way!
See? Over there!
What are they?
Graves.
It just gives me peace of mind.
I forge the swords to serve
as their grave markers.
It isn't as if anyone actually rests under them.
There aren't nearly enough for all of them,
but we often did this on the battlefield, right?
Two years...
More than enough time for someone to change.
While I remained mired in hatred,
Rickert did this.
He accepted their deaths.
He mourned and found a new way of life.
It's just like him, this vigorous strength.
I know I'm safe here,
but without my sword,
I can't sleep in the dark.
No...
I probably can't ever sleep at night
for the rest of my life.
You fled to be alone,
to use your personal hatred
to burn your very self.
I didn't run away...
I can't get away!
It's burned into my right eye,
that final terror and hatred.
I can never atone for this pitch black flame!
If I can't atone, and I can't run from it,
I must let it burn me.
I must let it engulf my enemies.
Keep bathing in blood,
killing,
and thirsting.
Forever alone.
Forever...
That's right.
I...
I left her in that state.
What right do I have now?
I abandoned Casca, who was
the Band of the Hawk itself.
I have no right to speak of
vengeance for the fallen.
You were captain of the
raiding party, weren't you?
You said something about dreams or whatever,
but you left for selfish reasons, didn't you?
You weren't there in our
hour of greatest need.
How can I call someone like
that a brother-in-arms?
You've left us, haven't you?
You have no obligation to go that far for us.
Take her with you, even if by force.
This time, you have to.
If you don't, she'll...
You'll fight your own war, won't you?
You have to go.
You have to go, even if you go alone.
That's right.
I left long ago.
At that moment, I lost the right...
I guess I started that war.
It's true that it wasn't what I wanted.
But at least it wasn't anything
that was forced on me.
It's a war I chose to take on myself.
But...
Even still...
Those camp fires back then...
They continue burning in my heart.
That's right.
Is this fragile, residual fire
the only thing keeping that black
flame from engulfing me?
Man...
Have I made
the same mistake again?
Hurry.
Go now...
No, not yet.
It's not too late, yet.
This time for sure...
I can't lose her ever again!
You're working hard!
H-Hey...
I thought you were asleep.
Well, yeah, but I'll just get
eaten if I stay asleep.
Oh.
Okay, I'll help, too!
As a power-up, let's add a drill
and a cutter on his false hand!
Well, that's...
Not a shoemaker's elf, but a blacksmith's, I see.
Master, why are you dressed like that?!
There's something I have to do.
D-Don't be reckless! I'll do it—
Shut up!
Take care of Erica for me.
Master...
She isn't my real daughter.
She was an orphan, who lost
her family in the war.
I only knew how to deal with iron.
But she made me into a pretty
decent human being.
But you know...
When you die,
it's good to plunge into it alone.
Master...
Tell that idiot not to turn into me.
How's the new armor?
The master readied it for you.
Also, there's a new weapon
that uses gunpowder.
And a new, improved bowgun
that doesn't require assembly
when you need it in a pinch.
Where are you off to now?
Have you heard of anywhere nearby
known as "holy ground"?
Holy ground, huh...
Now that I think of it, an old monastery
named St. Albion is three
days northeast of here.
It's called the Tower of Conviction.
The Tower of Conviction...
It's full of refugees.
Supposedly, heretics hid among them.
So now, the Holy See is sending
a grand inquisitor.
Basically, there'll be a witch trial...
But why are you asking?
Guts!
I think the possibility that Casca's there is low.
I have my reasons.
I'm grasping at straws,
but I have to trust my instincts.
Later.
I don't really get what's going on.
But I wonder what Casca's like.
Guts!
I'm counting on you to help Casca!
Promise me you'll come back.
Godo, you're a good smith!
I'll ask for help again when I return.
You and your big mouth, idiot.
Dad, you have to stay in bed!
I don't think we'll see each other again.
It's better than getting all weepy, for sure.
But when you're running toward a goal like that,
you'll let something pass by, unnoticed, again.
Whether you live or die,
you never get your way.
It's like a mass migration.
Disease and famine.
And now, Kushan's massive invasion...
In its time of weakness after the king's death,
Windham, the capital, was attacked and occupied.
Most of the retainers are missing,
including the royal heir,
Her Highness Charlotte.
When it rains, it pours...
Show some respect.
But if that's true, our destination, St. Albion,
is near the Midland border,
despite being within Holy See jurisdiction.
Kushans are considered our foes
by religion, aren't they?
Is this the right time for an inquisition?
If anything were amiss, the Holy See
would send new orders to us.
Until then, we only need carry
out the one we were given.
Yes, my lady.
Lady Farnese is in a worse mood than usual.
Is something wrong?
I-It's nothing!
Don't think about it.
It couldn't have been real!
I couldn't possibly do that.
It must have been a hallucination, a nightmare.
Right now, focus on escorting
the grand inquisitor!
Even if God never graces me with a miracle,
I need but pursue my faith!
God is too far removed from the likes of you.
No!
I...
Is it just a bad mood?
Those monsters...
I didn't imagine them.
It pains me to say it,
but the Black Swordsman is too
heavy a burden for Lady Farnese.
Not only was she relieved of her role
in the Black Swordsman's pursuit
after being blamed for his escape,
but the new mission is to escort that man?
Of course she's in low spirits...
Clear the way!
Watch out!
That's a giant carriage!
Shit! Who do they think they are?
Shh! Know your place!
That's the grand inquisitor's carriage.
Look at the red wheels, hoisted on high!
They're practically the banners of
Mozgus of the Bloody Bible.
There's no mistake.
The Mozgus?
The breaking wheel...
The skewering, water torture,
burning at the stake...
He's easily sentenced over five
hundred people to execution.
An exponential number more are
said to have died by torture.
He's hated by many...
An enemy attack?!
Die, Mozgus!
You killed my family!
My son!
My daughter!
I'll kill you!
We can't reach him through the refugees!
They've flanked us!
Show yourself, Mozgus!
Huh?
What?
What the...
Honestly, such a clamor...
God values silence.
Lord Mozgus, are you all right?
I apologize!
We were taken completely by surprise!
Lady Farnese, please rise.
God is generous to those who do His work.
It is fortunate that no one who serves
the Holy See has been injured.
That is due to God's grace.
I am humbled by your words.
I shall be diligent in my efforts from here.
And who may these men be?
They are torturers, working only for me.
After rigorous training and service,
they possess iron resolve.
They are always of great service to our work.
That is... very heartening to hear.
So, pray tell, why did you attack me?
Shit!
Let me go!
It was for revenge!
You burned the village, killing everyone!
You claimed it was a sanctuary for heretics!
I merely meted out impartial judgment,
in accordance with God's teachings—
How can you call it impartial?!
We only said we had to temporarily
suspend our tithes
because famine had exhausted our food stores!
But you ignored what we said!
Divine punishment...
You will face divine punishment!
Divine punishment?
How dare you speak of divine punishment,
you reprobate?!
You are an apostate, who dares turn on a cleric!
And you speak of divine punishment,
you depraved lot?
Nay, none other than our Holy See
has the right to speak for God in this world!
Lady Farnese...
Y-Yes?
What would you deem appropriate
punishment for ones such as they?
Those who plan to murder a man of
the cloth are typically condemned
to execution by fire or the breaking wheel.
You are most wise, Commander of
the Holy Iron Chain Knights.
That is most perceptive.
Then let us conduct a simplified trial here.
Here is my judgment.
All the accused are condemned
to the breaking wheel.
Forgive me!
Please! No!
N-Next.
Next!
Hey!
Help me!
Hey...
Don't involve yourself.
Hey, girl!
Are you one of them?
Wait! She isn't with them at all!
Shut up!
Come with us, too—
Wh-What, is she addled?
Hey, come!
Mercy!
No!
My name is Luca.
Are you okay?
What a gruesome spectacle.
I feel nauseated.
If you watch, you'll just be sickened.
Come.
Next Episode Preview
What an unexpected test of my blade.
I'm not a fan of being mocked.
I'm... I'm scared of everything!
The Kushans have no mercy, even for kids.
Heretics.
Next Episode
Tower of Conviction