Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey, talk about a reversal of fortunes, huh?
What was that?
Night of Miracles
She can't see you?
What does that even mean?
Well, how should I explain?
Oh, an old fortune teller with the traveling
entertainers used to say that...
Um, those with a rigid
world view can't see fae.
I think that was it...
I see.
A rigid world view, huh?
Guts!
I know.
Here they come.
My allies?
What?
What's happening?
Take a good look, with wide-open eyes.
They're miracles, sent to this world by God,
that you can't see just by worshiping an idol.
I see it now.
What is that?
That's where I was headed to begin with.
Though there's been lots of interference.
What's there?
Didn't you want to know what I was after?
Eh?
It's just as well.
I'll tell you now.
That is...
The estate of Count Lansdown,
who governed Midland's western outskirts.
Loving hunting and hounds, he built this
manse at which to while away his idleness.
The fire five years ago, which killed
the count and his retainers,
should have reduced it to mere ruins...
Come to think of it,
reports said that travelers and pilgrims
often go missing in these parts.
What a sad end for the former hounds.
They're excited by the smell of blood.
Impossible.
How can such things...
...even exist?
That's why I called them miracles.
How can you be terrified of
such a great opportunity?
As a believer, don't you have some phrase?
You could say, "Dear God..."
I've had my fill of miracles.
Enough to make me puke.
Come with me, or you'll be devoured!
Where am I?
Man, that was tough...
What, you even brought the horse?
Hey, Guts!
You seem not to have gotten
it through your skull—
Yeah, I know...
I'll never forget that you brought
me all the way here, horse.
Very good.
Man, those are a lot of heads.
Humans, I tell you...
Oh, Divine Lord, show mercy.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing really.
What in the world is this?
What misshapen, abhorrent creatures...
Does this have to do with what
Revelations foretold, as well?
Serpico?
Don't!
That idiot!
A man?
Who are you?
That's my line.
I am this place's keeper of the hounds.
Very well...
First, untie me!
I'll see that you are rewarded
handsomely for your aid!
I am...
I am in this state for reasons I cannot say,
but I am a legitimate Holy See knight.
I will ensure you are well-received.
Meat...
What?
It's easier to eat the way it is...
H-H-Hounds!
Don't be cruel to the hounds!
They're my... my family.
Don't hurt them!
You... You'll pay for this!
Even the master of the house...
is fed to the dogs if he... if he is cruel to them!
You killed the master of the house?
No, I ate him.
I... I haven't smelled anything
this good in a long time.
A high-quality noblewoman...
I kn-know... y-your smell...
That was the best prey.
You are a survivor from that day?
I won't be lame and try to
go easy with my injuries.
I couldn't care less if my arm gets ripped off.
For the first time in a long while, I remember
how it felt at the start of all this.
Thanks, it feels like crap.
Me... Me, too.
Thanks.
See, he's finally here.
My target, the one you
wanted to know about...
The Apostle.
Apostle?
That's right.
Eradicating every last one of these Apostles...
That is my goal.
Th-The moment that brand marked you...
Your... Your fate was set in stone.
You're just p-prey... meat... hunted...
s-struggling... crawling!
Like I said...
Don't be cruel to the hounds!
Guts, above you!
Right!
What's wrong with you, Guts?!
Do it like usual!
Meat... Meat!
Meat... Meat...
I'm tough and taste like shit...
It'll be fine.
After eating you,
I'll c-cleanse my palate...
with the woman-meat.
Th-That woman... is like the lady.
A noblewoman...
So soft.
M-Melting in your mouth...
The lady?
Th-The flavors are coming out.
Humans who oppose us...
are just food.
I gotta say, when it comes to eating,
you have no table manners.
Yeah.
M-Meat has high... and low grades...
People nice to me have... s-soft, sweet meat.
M-Meat from those... who call me ugly...
a-and inferior is low-grade!
Smelly meat... tough meat...
Then I doubt I'd taste good.
No hurry.
I'll know soon enough!
Hey, Guts!
Th-This is real.
This is a real, preserved human being!
Don't touch her!
Don't...
Don't touch the lady!
My lady!
Sh-She believed in me.
They looked down... on me
as ugly and inferior.
The lady was the only one...
who believed me, and I...
M-My lady!
So you dressed up the half-eaten
remains as a tribute to her?
Talk about twisted to the core.
Guts...
I will eradicate every last Apostle.
I'll give you a clean death, so talk.
How can I find them?
Them?
The God Hand.
I... I don't know!
I know nothing about them.
They are special...
R-Really, I d-don't know!
I said I don't know!
I don't understand.
I can't think of anything!
Not even a single prayer!
I... I don't... know...
I see.
I'll ride this horse!
Nope.
I'll ride woman.
Female. Meat.
Delicious!
No!
Don't run around if you want to live.
Ye...
Yes.
I'm just running around,
trembling with fear.
I couldn't even beseech God.
And I call myself His servant...
I've said His name a million times.
But I am only
weak,
wretched,
and powerless.
Just powerless?
Just powerless, so you are innocent?
Don't deceive yourself with pretty words.
Within you lies
a dark desire you cannot tell anyone else about.
You felt it...
You felt a dismal lust as you struck that man.
That wasn't the only time...
Even when whipping yourself
in the name of atonement,
you found pleasure within that agony...
There is no God in any of it.
This festering desire is the only truth.
God is too far removed from the likes of you.
Guts...
Hey.
What do you think you're doing?
Guts, she's...
You let yourself get possessed...
Pull this sword up very slowly...
Feel it with me... This pleasure.
Slowly tear me apart.
No!
Hey, you...
Kill him.
Kill that man.
Right now, right here!
Please calm down, Lady Farnese.
I don't know what happened,
but our original mission was
to capture him, remember?
You should avoid being swayed by—
I don't care!
Kill him!
To be blunt, I can't. Not me.
You saw it yourself, Commander.
He has superhuman strength.
I'd just die a meaningless death—
Ow.
Oh, Commander!
There you go, making our commander cry again.
Not my problem.
Well, we shall take our leave.
That is, if you are willing to let us go.
I think I owe you one.
Well, I suppose so.
Heh, fine.
Not a bad move, drawing your sword like that.
I'll say the same.
You are formidable.
So, till we meet again.
Hey, wait!
For now, it is farewell.
Same to you, pipsqueak.
What a joker.
But you know, I feel kind of
sorry for that Farnese girl.
She's like, all tightly wound.
I'm the one who's wound up.
First a ghost, and now a cleric.
Talk about annoying.
Commander, wait for me!
I have to kill him.
I have to.
I have to!
If I don't silence him...
If he continues to live, I...
They saw the same visions in their dreams.
There were villages decimated by disease,
and nations overrun by armies
that commanded giant beasts.
There were cities crushed by earthquakes,
and towns swallowed by floods.
The Sun hidden by a thick, black smoke,
and wandering throngs of starving people.
There were bodies of entire families,
and bodies of their neighbors.
Each saw a myriad of varieties,
but all pointed toward a singular intent.
Each enduring their own night,
the people were trapped in true darkness
that enveloped their shared world.
And amidst the ensuing chaos,
they observed with keen interest
a shining hawk, piercing the infinite gloom,
and descending upon the bloodstained land.
They knew immediately
that this was their greatest desire.
Charlotte...
Charlo...
Doctor?
Please bring his relatives.
Quickly, I beg you.
At last...
At long last, we'll have a new queen.
Her Majesty, Queen Charlotte.
Given her nature, she will appoint a regent.
We should plan accordingly...
Do those dolts even
understand what's happening?
It was only thanks to His Majesty
that we survived the war with Chuder.
The hawk...
The hawk will return.
A strange hawk of light that
the people of Windham... nay,
all of Midland saw in dreams.
Though His Majesty was noble and just,
he became inscrutable in many of his
actions after the Battle of Doldrey.
The Band of the Hawk's alleged treason...
Did that really happen?
Your Highness, please open the door!
What is the matter?
General Laban, well,
Her Highness hasn't left her
chambers in five whole days.
Only her favorite lady-in-waiting
is allowed to enter.
She's trying to persuade Her
Highness right now, but...
Your Highness...
Your Highness!
Allow me!
Your Highness,
His Majesty is in critical condition!
Your Highness!
Griffith...
Where are... you now?
Father!
His Majesty has passed away.
Now, of all times?
What will happen now?
Please save me, Lord Griffith!
The mountain's moving.
Next Episode Preview
Is Casca alive?
I'll never lose her again.
Come back again, no matter what.
There is something I must do.
You claim it's divine punishment?
Next Episode
Epiphany