Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Orders to return?
Why, on such short notice, Abbot?
It is a direct order from the Holy See.
It can be said that the heretics
have been sufficiently quelled.
I thank you for your long service.
Remnants may yet be hiding.
The people are still unsettled.
The investigations and sentencing
will take time to conclude.
In the meantime, what will you
do to maintain security?
You needn't worry yourself about that.
This directive was not addressed
to the Holy Iron Chain Knights.
But to you alone, Lady Farnese.
What?
I am to abandon my own troops?
I, the commander, should abandon our mission?
I do not understand.
I cannot accept!
As for your current mission,
having Vice-Commander Azan lead in
your stead should not be a problem.
Lady Farnese, it appears that
this directive comes, in part,
at the wish of Lord Vandimion, your father.
I ask you to understand.
Though this may be a holy mission,
your father does not wish you,
as a woman, to remain long
in such a gruesome place.
I...
House Vandimion funds the majority
of relief supplies for these refugees.
Lady Farnese!
Please wait, Lady Farnese...
Ow.
You told my father, didn't you?
Eh?
I know it all!
You report to my family on my actions.
You probably wrote that I am
joyously hunting heretics
and burning them at the stake, right?
That's...
Was it at my father's order?
You couldn't deny the master of the house.
Well...
But do not forget.
I am your master!
You swore your sword to me.
I am your only master.
Yes, my lady.
Do you hate me?
Why would I?
I have never met anyone as pathetic as you.
You blabbed everything before I
could take a single fingernail.
Sorry...
Having sold out your friend,
enjoy your last night alive.
Sorry... Sorry...
Please forgive me...
Blood Flow of the Dead
Well done, Lady Farnese.
It would not be an exaggeration to say
that we have captured nearly
all of the heretics at Albion.
Your reputation as the Holy Iron Chain
Knights' commander is well deserved.
No, it is thanks to God's grace.
By the way, your report indicates
that your men encountered several anomalies
while raiding the heretics' lair.
The cave was full of arcane drugs
and incense that the heretics use
during their rituals.
I believe they may have triggered
a mass hallucination.
According to the report,
there is one other thing.
The Black Swordsman, previously sought
by your knights, appeared?
Yes.
Hmm, but why?
H-Hey, stop.
This girl...
What about her?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just, when the Black
Swordsman appeared,
he seemed to be trying to rescue her.
Witch...
Please save us.
Reporting, sir.
The heretics' confessions indicate
that the girl is their priestess.
Or, perhaps, the very object of their faith.
The priestess of heretics, with ties
to the Black Swordsman...
Hmm...
This is a witch's brand indeed.
Evidently, we must take special
care in investigating this girl.
Casca!
Casca...
Let's go.
You two, stay hidden.
I know you want to hurry, but if
you cause a commotion,
you'll lose your chance to rescue her.
Huh? I haven't seen you around here.
I got a personal summons.
Sorry, but would you take a message?
I'm here for Jerome, of the
Holy Iron Chain Knights—
Huh? Did someone just pass?
I'm sure you imagined it...
Casca!
Wh-What is going on here?
That's...
Stay back, please!
Blood?
I hurt!
I'm starving...
I'm cold!
M-Monsters!
They eat humans.
Don't leave us behind!
Please hurry, Lady Farnese!
W-Wait!
Father Mozgus!
Father Mozgus, we must retreat!
Impertinent witch!
The front entrance is blocked.
Let's escape to the chapel.
Casca!
N-No way...
What is going on here?!
For now, let us ascend!
I shall explain later!
Y-You—
Where is my companion?
Then you did come here for the girl.
Answer me!
Th-That girl is in the cellar...
In the torture chamber...
The torture chamber.
Where is that?
I-It's no use. Even if you go there now...
In the cellar, there are...
There are so many.
Hey! Get your act together!
I don't know!
They shouldn't exist.
They can't exist. Not those things...
Take me to that torture chamber of yours.
No!
Who would go there again?
Sorry, but hurry it up...
I'm about to snap.
I'm so useless...
I'm a worthless human being.
Only one more night.
Even now, I'm only worried about myself.
Because of me, by now, Elaine must be...
But...
I don't want to die—
Retreat! Retreat!
Up! Run up!
What about the prisoners?
Who cares? Abandon them!
What's going on?
U-Um, did...
Did something happen?
Monsters!
Monsters...
Hello?
It's coming from below?
Guards! Please open the door!
No!
Please, someone!
Found you...
Hey.
Luca!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The emotional reunion will have to wait.
Something is wrong.
Hey, now! What are you doing?
Run!
That way!
It's the plan. It's a diversion.
We'll use them as bait, and escape
while they distract the guards.
Hey, I may not look it, but I
am a heretic hunter.
You're saying that, even now?
You're an accomplice.
Damned brat...
Sorry, Jerome.
I didn't mean to involve you.
Honestly, I've reached
the end of my rope.
But I guess it's all good.
I didn't like the mission, anyway.
And this gives me a break.
Ruining my future over a woman
may be fitting for a prodigal son like me.
Jerome...
All right. With that decided,
let's get out of Albion.
Sorry, we have one more.
Nina, where's Elaine?
I...
d-don't know.
She's probably in the basement.
Everyone's gone. This is your chance.
What's that?
What's going on here?
Impossible.
Only a while ago...
That...
That thing did it!
Hey.
What are you doing?
Trying to get heavy armor
and run down the enemy.
I sneaked in here to save Casca.
But those things came out of
the woodwork in the room.
Where is...
Where is Casca?
Casca was swallowed up by them...
Oh, but something didn't make sense.
Everyone else melted right away,
but Casca didn't.
Even though she was swallowed,
I could still sense her presence.
What is he doing?
I think she's okay.
No, I'm sure of it!
Wh-What is that?
This way.
That's right...
Back then...
Hey, you're free to go.
W-Wait!
I'll come, too!
Please stay back!
The doors will give way soon!
There is nothing to fear!
This is our faith's moment of truth.
We do not pray to God for salvation.
Faith requires everything from us.
Repent, evil spirits!
I have found that faith means death!
Come at me!
Master, draw back!
No matter what may challenge me...
Hey, mister!
I need to go downstairs!
Escaping is the priority!
Elaine, I hope you're safe...
Got it!
If I remember right, the chapel's ahead.
Those doors are pretty thick.
Ideal for holing up in—
Sh-Shit!
Luca!
Close your eyes!
Stones...
Stones!
I have witnessed a miracle!
This is God's will.
I am to guide the people with this power.
Elaine...
That's Elaine!
Hey, square-face!
Hand over that lady!
That will not do.
This witch is the origin of the
evil that festers in Albion.
I am destined to demonstrate
God's victory to the people, by burning
this witch at the stake.
What witch are you talking about?
You guys look tons more suspicious!
Guess we have no choice...
I see.
You seek to interfere with my sacred duty?
My disciples have no mercy
toward enemies of God.
Hey, those are above my pay grade!
Luca!
M-Mister, another attack!
The next one's coming!
It's fine! Pull them up, fast!
Here, this way.
The presence is getting stronger.
W-Wait...
Luca...
Nina...
So heavy.
This is how heavy Luca is.
I'm holding Luca's life in my hands.
Right now, all that she is rests in my hands.
If I were to let go...
Jerome, take care of Nina.
Huh?
Hurry! Run!
Luca!
Luca...
Why?
Huh?
What's that?
Is it Death?
Wh-What was that?
I-It flew?
Luca...
I'd forgotten about them!
Get down!
Um, you're Death... Right?
Girl, why did you choose to die?
H-Hey, don't go there...
I'm not that noble.
Look, that tower is really tall.
But it has a couple layers, see?
I wouldn't have slammed into the ground.
I thought I could maybe get
away with a broken leg,
as long as the roofs were wooden...
Well, now that I think about it,
it was pretty reckless.
I thought it was the only choice,
so everyone could live, but...
But I guess it didn't work, after all.
I got lucky and was spared pain,
but this doesn't really feel like Heaven.
It is not.
This is a resting place for the dead,
at the foot of that tower.
Huh?
Oh, you mean I'm still alive?
So it seems.
If you wish to stay so, do not move.
Show yourself!
What?
So you are the famed Black Swordsman...
I do not know what you seek to accomplish,
but I cannot let you have this witch,
in the name of God's justice!
Fool, you seek to rebel against God!
I will have you atone with blood.
An Apostle?
No, it's different.
My brand senses something else.
They'll be formidable foes.
And seven of them, at that.
Guts, behind you!
W-Wow!
It was only possible with my assist.
Brat, you've got something
strange on your head...
When did they...
I can't avoid it.
What?
Just one more step.
Next Episode Preview
What's happening?
Screams?
It begins...
Elven Lethal Head-Strike!
We desire only one thing.
Next Episode
Hell's Angels