Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Yeah, struggle!
It's more fun when they fight!
What's with her?
Hey, you guys!
Luca...
Huh?
What?
Hey, what's wrong?
Starving!
Wh-What's going on here?
Meat! Meat!
Elaine!
Elaine, you...
A witch...
She's a witch.
Like I said, you're just causing trouble.
Don't say that. Please accept.
Please give this to...
You aren't giving me a choice.
I'll take it, but I don't need the
attention in broad daylight.
Leave for now, will you?
This isn't good...
Luca, what will we do?
At this rate, someone will report us.
Even if they don't, we'll be
noticed by the heretic hunters.
It's just a matter of time!
And when... When that
happens, what then?
I mean, I'm actually a—
Hey, Nina... Calm down—
How can I?!
Even if that doesn't happen,
if they find Joachim's body, I'll be...
Nina...
Let's abandon her.
Huh?
Let's abandon that girl.
Nina, not this again!
This isn't going to work!
If we let that girl stick around,
we'll be finished for sure!
It'll be fine...
Elaine will be fine on her own!
She's really special, you see?!
I bet my people will treat her well
if we leave her with them!
We've already taken care of her enough!
No way will I abandon anyone.
Not you or Elaine.
Luca...
Help, Luca!
What's wrong?
Pepe's...
Pepe's been taken by the hunters!
The Black Witch
No! Let me go!
Shut up!
We've had a report!
During your trial, you can contest
the claims as much as you like.
That's a girl with Luca.
Pepe...
Come to think of it, they've been
doing well for themselves lately.
I'll be raped!
I'll be killed!
Oh, God!
Damn you commoners...
Shut up, will you?!
You filthy lot never say a word
of prayer in your lives.
But once you're in trouble, you take God's
name in vain without hesitation.
How wretched!
How servile!
You shameless worm!
Don't be so high and mighty
when you're catching people
without risking a hair on your head!
Luca...
Please have mercy.
Oh?
If you defend her,
you will also be imprisoned.
Now you're threatening people again, to shut
them up when they try to say anything.
You flash your swords.
You judge people from your comfortable towers.
Do you people think you're angels or something?
Is that all you have to say, miss?
Pepe!
Luca!
Who would dare?
You're...
The Black Swordsman!
The Black Swordsman?
How opportune...
This must be God's grace at work.
We won't let you go this—
Based on what that woman said,
you seem to be the one
leading the witch hunt.
Answer me.
Among the ones you captured, was there
a woman with a brand on her chest?
A brand?
I... I don't know!
How dare you?
W-Wow...
He cut them in half!
Hey, ladies.
Let's get going.
Hey, your speech was pretty cool.
I think I'm falling for you!
Who's this monkey?
This is my property. He's Dropey, my villa.
Who're you calling "Dropey"?
And the one causing trouble
is Guts, my main estate, Black Iron Castle.
There's something...
...weird.
You call this a holy land?
What a bad joke.
It's more like a dump.
Sorry for my delayed introduction.
My name is Puck.
I own both properties.
None of this makes any sense.
Okay, please stay still.
My pain's going away...
Out! Out of the way!
Open the way!
Report this to the main troops!
Asking a peon's getting me nowhere.
I'll just have to go over there myself.
A woman with a brand.
Is that what you said?
Do you know her?
Hey, Guts...
First, thank you for—
I don't give a shit about that!
That's the same as the one on our Elaine.
Tell me...
Where is she? Where is Casca?!
Luca's late.
Is she okay?
If Luca's been caught,
what will I do?
That's right.
If that's what happened,
and the heretic hunters come...
I have to run now!
Let's abandon that girl.
We've already taken care of her enough!
I...
Why am I like this?
Elaine, come with me.
Don't worry. I'll take care of you.
I can't leave you behind.
It's scary and lonely alone.
Casca...
I feel like decades have passed
since I last saw you.
Are you still the same as before?
The same as when you broke,
and time ground to a halt?
Oh, so that's her.
Hey, sir.
What are you to Elaine... I mean, Casca?
Hey!
Well, never mind.
I kind of figured it out.
Elaine! Nina!
Don't just stand there. Go inside.
Huh?
No one's here.
Oh, no! Were the heretic hunters here?
But the place isn't ransacked.
Nina's things are missing.
Wait, did she...
Casca!
I'm okay...
Let's go.
We have come to welcome
you, Lady Priestess.
You...
Ha.
Even if we split up to find her,
this place's too big...
Dropey, why do you keep following Guts?
You're even helping him look for someone.
And why are you on top of my head?
You wouldn't recognize Casca on your own.
And you know what she looks like?
I saw her with my mind.
What's that?
Don't look!
Aren't you scaring the shit out of everyone?
They're all scaredy-cats.
Still, it's strange.
In places with lots of people, I should
become harder to see.
I wonder if this place is special.
Anyway, I don't get this whole
witch hunt or whatever deal,
but everyone's so scared!
Man, talk about a shit-show.
After running from the Kushans,
they have to fear being reported.
They're drowning in quicksand.
And you're different, Dropey?
'Course I am!
This is a great chance for a man
to advance in the world.
I don't need money to start, either.
This is good enough.
That's why you want to be Guts' apprentice?
You don't get it.
If I have to bow and scrape
to someone just to learn...
I'd rather follow them around and
steal their skills like a man!
You're a thief, through and through, huh?
Well, but if I do him a favor here,
I won't have to sneak around.
It's all about give and take, you know?
Hmm?
Let me go!
A bandaged woman...
Are they being kidnapped?
What should we do?
If we go back to tell Guts, we'll lose them.
But we can't take on that
many people, either...
For now,
we'll follow them.
Your specialty.
We have news.
The heretics' lair?
This one claims he managed to escape,
after being abducted by heretics.
Based on his account and
description of the place,
he seems to be telling the truth.
Very well, we shall go forth!
There is another report.
What?
Some of our men, transporting heretics
from the refugee camp,
have been attacked.
There have been several casualties.
How many enemies are we talking about?
According to the knights
who retreated, only one.
What?
A giant man in black, with a
sword as long as he is tall.
The Black Swordsman...
Is this true?
Yes, sir. We believe so.
This must be God's hand at work!
We will not let him go a second time!
Unfortunately, we must ask you
to take us to the heretics' lair.
Of course.
Bingo.
Guess this is the heretics' lair.
Hear me!
Tonight will be a holy night,
which will be retold by posterity.
That tower has become a source of clever lies,
a den for swine who seek
to oppress and rule us!
But we know the truth.
We know whom we should truly worship.
We know who possesses true power!
In advance of the promised day,
our master has given us a sign tonight!
It's Casca!
That's her...
It is our priestess, the Black Witch!
She is the symbol of our faith.
She is a miracle in herself!
And on this joyous eve,
one of the faithful will be fortunate
enough to receive more honor
than she deserves!
No!
Let me go!
It's the girl who was with Casca!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think something bad's gonna happen.
Rejoice, Daughter Nina.
Your sin, in trying to keep her to yourself,
will be redeemed by your act of duty.
We will now remove this one's heart,
as an offering to the witch.
After, we will have her consummate
her union with our Great Goat,
to become a true member of our family!
Shit's getting real!
What now, what now, what now?
If we try to get Guts now,
we won't be back in time!
Hey, Puck...
I'll buy us time.
Fly as fast as you can, and get Guts.
I didn't know you had actual skills.
Shut up!
I kind of have the advantage here, you know?
Oh, no...
N-No!
Oh, nice! Well done!
You think better of me now?
I'd rather not have gone this
route if I could've helped it.
It's a cheap trick for a man who's gonna
make it big with his sword!
A thief... who throws rocks...
"Isidoro" means "rock-throwing thief"!
I knew you'd say that.
Hey, you cultist asses!
Quit your rites and shit in that
crappy, moldy hole of yours!
I'm gonna report you!
Okay, go, Puck!
Roger.
Throw!
Throw until your iron left arm breaks!
Make sure you talk me up to Guts!
Drag him down!
We'll sacrifice him, too.
Ha!
You worthless shits can't do anything
unless you're in a mob!
You're the ones to be sacrificed
to my ambition!
Take that!
Fools!
All critical hits!
Lots of rocks here.
It's been a year since I left my village.
Wandering aimlessly through areas where
bandits and Kushans roamed,
there were lots of near misses and
days with no food or drink.
But it's all paid off.
I have a big chance for the taking,
waiting right in front of me.
There's no way I'm gonna miss it.
As long as I can get through this,
I can achieve my goal!
I will win, no matter what it takes!
What're you all doing?!
That boy... What is he doing?
Elaine, let's get out while we can.
What's wrong?
What the hell?
Elaine?
That's the place.
Good!
Units one through four, follow me!
The rest of you, spread out
and cover the entrance.
Capture all who attempt escape!
Forward!
Subdue them!
Heretics!
Resistance will be dealt with harshly!
Help...
Wh-What?
What's going on with them?
H-Help!
Wh-What?
Who are they?
Vice-Commander Azan!
Azan, what is going on?
I have heard that heretics employ
various drugs during their rites.
Perhaps some of them turn men into beasts?
Drugs... I see.
Beware.
They now have the strength
of many grown men.
Drugs?
Could drugs really be the cause?
This is like...
It reminds me of when...
Special throw... It'll split
your head right open!
Yeah!
But... What the hell's going on?
The hunter troops are coming in droves, too.
Shit's really going down now.
You weirdo!
Hup!
Hmph!
Take that!
A-Am I gonna die?
H-Hey.
Okay, ladies, time to get outta here.
Who are you?
I'm Isidoro.
The details can wait!
Thanks.
But...
We can't go that way.
Hmm?
A-ha...
Hurry!
M-My horns are stuck.
Just leave them behind!
H-Help—
Lady Farnese!
This cannot continue...
We should retreat and regroup.
You're right.
A boy?
Why is a boy here?
This is...
An actual monster?
Are they all monsters?
It's like before.
It's just like that night...
You're knights, aren't you?
Hold the line and fight, cowards!
Elaine!
Man, I'm freezing...
Seems they're having a lot of trouble inside.
Huh? Did something pass through?
Huh?
You asses!
Witch...
Consummate...
Become family...
You pervy goat!
Don't get so excited!
Next Episode Preview
No! Do not let him get away!
Baeeeeeeh!
I'm leaving Casca to you.
Luca, I can't. I...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Black Swordsman.
Next Episode
Reunion in the Den of Evil