Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hurry up!
Burn her!
We'll be saved if we burn her!
Out of the way!
It's just like that time.
It's going to end the same way.
Thank you.
If you want to live, you will
leave this land at once.
As much as I want to get the
hell out of here...
I can't.
Not to mention that it doesn't seem
I can do anything about this alone.
I might just be trying to act tough,
but I have to go.
I see.
Thanks for everything, Death... See you!
It's as though she's going to go
take care of a trivial matter.
Is that a fool's courage or...
No matter.
Everything is following the
same path as before.
Unfortunately, no man possesses the means
to change this festival's outcome.
We are already caught in the whorls of karma.
Shadows of Ideas
Soon...  Very soon, my life will also end.
That is when...
Ultimately, I want see my world
from above as it's destroyed.
If, like those inquisitors,
I had met that priest,
would my life have been any different?
Would I have been a someone,
who had encountered another?
But I met no one...
Actually,
I existed only to look down upon this
world from my summit of loneliness.
I believe that now.
This world that existed only for me to
look up to, as it looked down upon me.
This is enough... Let it all end.
This infant saved that witch numerous times.
This is a body of flesh, but it is not human.
It is dying.
You are the same as me, grotesque infant?
Let us go together.
At least,
you can dream, using the new world
within me as your cradle.
You stupid people!
You're doing the same thing as those cultists!
What are you going to do?
I don't think throwing rocks will work this time.
Hurry it up!
But wow, I can't believe we're all alive.
Come on! Walk faster, you cultist!
Listen, we'll run at the first chance we get.
Are you all right?
I can't believe we got stuck
walking with these two...
I don't think they've figured us out,
but I've got to think of a way
to get out of here fast—
Hey, old man!
You showed up at the perfect time!
Wh-Who's that boy? That brat...
Huh? I can't hear you!
Just come here, and help me out!
I'll just go see what's going on.
If you'll excuse me!
That stupid brat!
Are you all right with this?
Burn! Burn her!
Hurry up and do it!
Now, hurry... Light the purifying flames.
Father Mozgus!
The whorls of karma... However...
Hey, are you serious?
I've been falling a lot lately,
so I've been getting damn used to it!
It doesn't mean
all of it...
Now, girl!
...will be the same.
That will not be!
You will not escape.
On the contrary,
you may not be the shadow on the water.
But a fish that breaks the water's surface.
Something black just...
Father Mozgus!
The great angel...
The great angel was defeated!
The great angel... That black demon!
What?
I just saw something from
the corner of my eye.
That's...
Casca!
Don't think that I'm gonna
let you keep stealing her!
Is an angel supposed to take a cut
of the action from a thief?
Another one's coming!
This brat is the only criminal here!
Please spare me!
What?
Stay back, stay back, stay back, stay back!
Old man...
Now, I've done it...
There's no way for me to get out of this now.
You fool who fears not God...
You will swiftly receive divine punishment!
In God's stead, I shall punish you.
Behold! Father Mozgus has revived!
He plans to fight that demon for our sakes!
Father Mozgus... Your form...
An angel?
No, more like a monster.
No matter how much of your evil
strength you use, it is futile.
Behold!
This is what deflected that impure blade.
This is the source of my faith!
As long as I hold the scripture to me,
harming my body is impossible.
The scripture's been cut through...
So that monster's basically just super hard?
You twins! Capture the witch!
The rest can die by the saw.
Hey!
The fact that you still live
means that my four disciples have
been summoned to Heaven...
I shall tear you limb from limb
as a tribute to them!
His strength equals that of an apostle.
And he's even tougher.
Come, mighty strength!
Come, superhuman strength!
Shit! They're coming again!
Now, now, if you don't pay attention...
God Thousand-Strike Cannon.
God Breath!
I'll shut that mouth of yours, so you
never utter a stupid sermon again.
How's that?
That will not suffice...
to cut through the armor I have received
from God!
He probably won't have a chance
to lend us a hand...
Quit whining!
Thanks to Guts, we only need
to deal with two of them.
And whose fault is it that I'm
in this mess? Damn it...
If I stay here any longer, I'll be
killed along with them.
I'm sorry, Elaine!
You idiot!
No, wait.
Are you all right?!
She's alive. I still feel her presence.
Hey, stop...
Damn it, they're just hovering above us!
If we could just stop their
movement for a second...
Leave that to me!
I'm not doing it anymore.
Wait! At this rate, I wouldn't
mind help from an elf!
At this rate?
Well, sorry! Look, they're coming!
What're you gonna do?!
Mark this well, monkey child!
Behold the sight of the true ruler of the skies!
Puck Spark!
He actually...
did it!
You're truly a terrifying brat.
The twins... How dare you?
Curse you!
Do you not fear God?
You dare get in the way of my
holy mission, you devils?
If you want to appease your God so much,
why not split your head open and offer it up?!
I won't let you lay another
finger on that woman.
It's moving again!
Father Mozgus!
Save us!
Oh, God!
Great angel!
Save us!
God Thousand-Strike Cannon.
I can't dodge completely.
And my attacks have no effect.
What am I supposed to...
It feels like being punched by a boulder.
Can you not hear those voices praying?
All of those here, right now,
have made their hearts one,
praying for salvation.
Are you saying you do not care
if the lives of the thousands
of true believers are lost in
exchange for that evil witch's life?
Stop being so pretentious!
How will burning the lady
save all those idiots?
Please hurry!
Please burn the witch!
Shut the hell up.
All they do is pray...
When they're in trouble,
all they do is try to save themselves...
Those tens of thousands don't have the
right to depend on a single woman!
Prayer is the sign of faith itself!
You must pray and offer yourself to God.
That is true faith!
You brazen fool, who knows not prayer,
repent!
God Pressure!
An unbeliever like you will
never witness miracles.
Repent by throwing yourself
into the purifying flames!
I tend to act first,
rather than wait for some great miracle...
I think your scripture
is about to let you down.
You're protecting yourself with
what you believe in most.
But if you look at it another way,
that's your weak point.
If you meet your God, say this for me...
Leave me the hell alone!
Oh, God... I am coming home to you...
Allow me, at least, to... take this
heathen with me!
I'm gonna pass.
It's your time to shine for your faith in God.
But I'll be punished if I intrude.
Fly up to heaven...
by your own damned self!
N-No!
Oh, God!
It hurts!
Why?
Someone...
It's so dark.
Starving...
Damn it!
Damn...
Kill her!
Kill that woman!
Please!
Would you shut your...
You fool!
Hurry!
Casca, are you okay?
Whoa! Casca!
The tower!
Run into the tower!
Head up higher!
The front's no use!
Head to the back!
Vice-commander, the masses
are flooding into the tower.
There is no other path.
We have no choice... Retreat!
All units, cover the masses!
But there are monsters in the tower!
It's better than being here!
Do not falter. Get as many inside as you can!
Vice-commander!
What?
Wait!
Many people are still out here!
Who cares?
Hurry up and shut the doors!
Shut them! Hurry!
Wait! There are still women and children!
Let us in!
No...
How could this have happened again?
Vice-commander, what should we...
Form up, and protect the women and children!
Only those who do not lose hope until
the very end are true knights.
Listen well. Now is the time that
we show what true knights are!
Yeah!
Crap... At this rate,
it's gonna climb up here!
Maybe it's about time that I leave.
Damn it, what are we supposed to...
Fire.
Look.
I get it... The creepy-crawly
blob is avoiding the fire...
Seems he was more useful in death.
Father Mozgus...
If you don't want to die,
pick up one of those.
I don't do well with fire...
Like that matters!
All right!
Hey...
Rather than staying up here,
why not head into the tower?
That'd be like jumping into a feeding trough.
Most of that will undoubtedly
go into the tower.
No point in holing up there,
when that'll just break through.
Not to mention, it'll be dawn soon.
That thing will either disappear or
weaken when the sun hits it.
But there won't be any sunlight in the tower.
The sun will shine brightest here.
We just have to last until morning.
We're going to survive.
We'll cut through to our survival.
Cut through!
Next Episode Preview
Being scared means that I want to live!!
I had forgotten.
That this is a world where the sun rises...
They're celebrating?!
Everything is being fulfilled by one voice.
Next Episode
Those Who Cling, Those Who Struggle